(This show features indirect advertisements.)
(Running Man)
- It's really hot. - It's so hot.
- I'm drenched in sweat. - It's hot.
(In the middle of summer, with the heat at its peak)
Hello.
Okay.
(The members have gathered at Gwangmyeong Cave.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello. It's so hot today.
- The weather is insane. - It's sweltering hot.
We came here about ten years ago.
We did?
(Filmed at Gwangmyeong Cave 9 years ago)
- We came here before? - This is my first time here.
What did we do here?
- When was that? - We played games in there.
(Blurry)
We went in there?
I remember this.
- What? - Going in there.
- You're lying. - You're lying.
I'm serious. Kwang Soo did this here.
(Disbelief)
Ji Hyo, are you sure you remember that?
This is where Kwang Soo did this.
- The fresh cream bomb thing. - Really? Here?
- Yes. - That's true.
(It's true!)
- Really? - See?
Ji Hyo, you're healthy.
(Congratulations!)
(Ji Hyo's still got it!)
She's not the old Ji Hyo anymore.
(Full of confidence)
I remember what everyone else forgot.
- There's the image behind us. - The cave.
(The display comes on as Ji Hyo's health is being celebrated.)
This place has gotten so much prettier.
They did a great job decorating it. It's so nicely put together.
- Ji Hyo remembers it. - Right. We've been here before.
With those glasses on,
- are you going back to Turbo days? - No.
The glare was just too much.
- You're wearing sunglasses now. - I flew in...
(Kim Turbo returned from Jeju Island this morning.)
from Jeju on the morning flight.
He said he was in Jeju,
so I asked what brought him there.
The thing is, FC Bayern Munich came...
(Jeju Island)
- to Jeju Island to play. - Yes.
(A friendly match between Munich and Jeju FC was on August 4.)
- On Jeju Island? - Against Jeju SK FC.
- That's right. - You really are the KFA President.
- But... - You're running the KFA.
Is this a buildup?
Obviously, he's the future president.
- What... - But this is...
- His moves are totally... - This is a buildup for a campaign.
I met Min Jae.
He went, "You need to be the KFA President."
If the opportunity came up, would you take on the role?
If it's for the future of Korean soccer,
I'd do it even out of my own pocket.
(What?)
Seriously?
So the rumor already reached him?
(Rumors of Soccer Kim running for chairman have even reached Munich.)
Min Jae saw that too.
If you really end up as president...
That's really amazing.
- What's that? We have news? - What?
(Another news worth celebrating)
I see. It hit 100 million views.
(Ha-Byul couple's short-form video has reached 100 million views.)
- That's right. - That's what we did.
This is insane.
- It's 100 million views. - We started it together.
TikTok Global...
(Every video the Viral Monster uploads is a hit.)
even called this the best case...
- from South Korea. - Really?
You might get a little sensitive...
- if I say this, - What?
but the era of Grandpa TikTok is over.
- It's the era of Uncle TikTok. - Grandpa TikTok?
- It's the era of Uncle TikTok. - Uncle TikTok.
(Grandpa TikTok's counterattack)
But my total views...
are already over 200 million.
Yes, but I hit 100 million views on just a single video.
- On just a single video? - You got 100 million on 1 video?
(Startled)
- With only one video? - That's crazy.
(Not bad.)
It was the most-viewed video in the entire country last week.
(Bragging in front of the grandpa)
- Haha. - Yes.
So you hit 100 million views,
Right. But no one knows.
but did your concert sell out all 470 seats or not?
(Concert)
- Did it sell out? - Now, I have...
("We Never Die")
300 seats left.
- What? - It didn't sell out yet?
Are you talking about the 300 bags of offering rice left over?
Haha, I bought two tickets.
- It sounds like offering rice. - I paid for the tickets.
I'll buy more.
- What happened? - I'll bring all my acquaintances.
His video got 100 million views, but his concert has 300 seats left.
This side is a completely different world.
(100 Million Views on TikTok, 300 Available Seats in Real Life)
- It's too different. - The gap between them is insane.
Between 100 million views and 400 seats...
- You still have 300 seats left? - It's so confusing.
(Please support the real-life version of Haha as well.)
- It really is. - What?
(Running Man Kids Lee Won)
Running Man Kids?
(Haha took something out.)
You even prepared this?
- What? - What's that?
(Shoutout to Running Man Kids after Nam Hyeong Ju)
- You're unbelievable. - Nam Hyeong Ju!
- This is driving me crazy. - Haha.
You just need to stick to promoting your concert.
(Running Man Kids Lee Won)
- It's not like that. - Okay.
The Running Man Kids are lining up...
- They want you to do this? - to audition for me right now!
- I see. - The thing is,
I'm worried he'll start charging them ten cents each.
- Seriously. - Running Man Kids, rise up!
(Lee Won donated 10 cents: A shoutout, please!)
This is ridiculous.
Running Man Kids, assemble!
- I'm 100 percent sure... - He has an ulterior motive.
- That's enough. - Don't try...
(Dedicated to the point of preparing a banner)
to build clout like that.
Stop using the young kids.
Running Man Kids!
(Slandering)
He’s doing all this to turn it into cash.
He's doing all this just to cash out on TikTok.
He's begging for views off these kids.
(Uncle TikTok makes the most of his moment.)
Even just standing still takes your breath away today,
(A record-breaking heatwave today)
with the highest temperature reaching 37°C.
- I see. - I'm dripping with sweat now.
I think I might be getting heat exhaustion.
- I'm sweating buckets now. - It's really hot.
They say the Yangsan area is exceptionally scorching now.
("Yangsan Reached 42.5°C, Extreme Heatwave in Korea")
Yes. Areas like Yangsan are reportedly topping 40°C.
It must be really tough.
- Yes. - It's just too hot.
(And so, the course prepared for today)
Today, we will find a cool getaway...
(Visiting cool spots to beat the heat)
to escape this brutal heatwave...
- and beat the heat. - Okay.
- Nice. - We're heading somewhere cool?
This is what we need.
(Cheering)
- I love it. - Great.
Our first destination is...
- Gwangmyeong Cave. - It's a cave.
(Vacation Course)
(Cave exploration)
It's perfect for summer.
Gwangmyeong Cave.
It was a gold mine...
(Gwangmyeong Cave)
that had been excavated since 1912,
(A gold mine where gold was mined as far back as 1912)
but it has now transformed into a top landmark...
(Now a popular tourist attraction and a sought-after vacation spot)
welcoming over a million visitors a year.
The inside of the cave is about 12°C all year round,
- keeping it delightfully cool. - Really?
(Great!)
- That sounds nice. - Let's hurry and get inside.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Today, you'll get to see an exclusive area...
(Today's special course)
that hasn't been opened to the public in 114 years.
- Really? - What's that?
- Why? - That sounds amazing.
- Let's step inside the cave then. - Let's go.
(Heading into the cave to escape from the heat)
- For 114 years? - That's great.
It must be cool.
- It's hot. - It's scorching hot.
- I'm feeling hot. - It's insane.
(The heat is already suffocating, even after just a few steps.)
- It's too hot. - It's hot.
- Hello. - Hello.
In front of the entrance...
(A food zone that instantly catches the eye)
- They have a lot of good food here. - Hey.
We should eat some cave bread.
Let's eat some cave bread.
(Seok Sam still has an appetite even in this heat.)
Who wants cave bread?
We should try one.
- Why don't we... - We should eat when we get there.
- Why? - Let's just go, Seok Jin.
(Whining)
- We will get some food there. - The cave bread looks delicious.
- Gosh, seriously... - The cave bread looks delicious.
(Eventually, they stop in front of the cave bread.)
Let's try it. It's 10 dollars for 3.
- It does look good. - It looks delicious.
(Gwangmyeong Cave)
- Shall we eat? - The youngest one should buy it.
Let's eat. Come here.
Ye Eun, you should pay.
(Rushing over as if they had been waiting)
When we're in a place like this, we should eat this.
We need to boost the local economy.
I'll pay.
- No, Seok Jin. - No. Wait.
(Big Bro offers to treat everyone.)
- Seok Jin. - I'll pay.
It's not like you're making good money.
- Right. - I'm making good money.
- Seok Jin. - My stock...
- My stock portfolio crashed, but... - Buy it with your pension money.
(The elder lost a lot in today's ever-changing stock market.)
- Go. - Buy it later with your pension.
You can buy us food when you get your pension.
(Grabbing the production crew's credit card)
They gave us this card.
All right, Seok Jin.
Why did you give him this card?
We will tally up the total amount later...
- and have one of you pay for it. - We do that?
(The vacation expenses will be tallied and settled later.)
and have one of you pay for it.
- We do that? - All right. Use the card then.
It's 10 dollars for 3.
- We should buy 9. - Right. We should buy 9.
Why are we buying 9 when we're 7 people?
- I know. - Because they come in threes.
- No. We will have 2 left. - It's 10 dollars for 3.
- Wait. - No.
- We will have seven. - To boost the local economy.
- We will have 9. - We will have 9.
But we will have two left.
To boost the local economy.
(Paid 30 dollars for 9)
- Someone will eat it. - We can eat them all.
The bread is quite big.
It looks delicious.
Thank you.
I love red beans.
(Smiling)
This is really pretty.
(The ultimate tourist spot rule is to grab the local specialty bread.)
- Yes, it's pretty. - Look at this.
- It's delicious. - Look.
- It's good, right? - It is tasty.
- Here. - It's shaped like a lucky pouch.
(They give the remaining 2 to the production crew.)
You can eat this.
(Exclaiming)
Thank you.
This is really good.
(Impressed)
Do you like it?
- I want to eat it with some coffee. - It's good.
(The snack lovers eat snacks all year round.)
- I love this. - It's so good.
(They each grab a piece of bread and head off,)
It's unbelievable.
(leaving the bill for later.)
- I know. - It's delicious.
- We've been here before? - It's an uphill climb.
(As they walk up the hill...)
- Let's go. - Hello.
- It's too hot. - Hello.
It's hot.
(They finally reach the cave entrance, drenched in sweat.)
- Hello. - It's hot.
- My throat is too dry. - It's too hot.
It's cool here. I'm feeling something cool.
- It's coming. - I'm feeling it.
- It's cool. - The AC breeze is coming.
(Gwangmyeong Cave)
- It's cool. - I'm feeling the cool air.
This is nice. Let's hurry and go inside.
(Cool air blows out from the cave entrance)
It's really cool.
- It's cool already. - Hello.
(They rush into the cave.)
- They say it's cold in there. - This is like...
- This is really nice. - It's cool.
It feels like the AC is on.
I love this.
It's nice.
- It's so cool. - Isn't this nice?
(It's paradise in here!)
- The AC is on. - My sweat cooled down right away.
- It's like the AC. - This is really nice.
(Cooling himself down)
Hey, maybe we'd need to put on some clothes.
- It's so cool. - My sweat dried right up.
It feels like the AC is on.
(The natural cave air is cooler than any AC breeze.)
Wind Road.
The AC is not on, is it?
It's not the AC.
- Is this natural? - It's the cave's natural breeze.
This is really nice.
- It's really cool. - It's 37°C outside.
This is really cool.
(A huge fridge gifted by nature)
It feels fake. It's like the AC is on.
Hello.
They are wearing long puffer jackets here.
(The staff is working with a long puffer on.)
They are working in long puffer jackets.
(As they walk, cooling off from the heat...)
- My goodness. - Look at that.
- This is beautiful. - This looks really nice.
- What's all this? - It's prettier than last time.
- This is like the movie "Avatar." - I know.
- It does look like that. - It's like "Avatar."
- It's the "Avatar" world. - It's even prettier than before.
(A beautiful space that reminds them of Kwang Soo appears.)
It's the "Avatar" world.
- This is amazing. - It does look like "Avatar."
- This is gorgeous. - It's so beautiful.
Toruk Makto.
Song Yi would love this place.
- Song Yi will love it. - I remember.
(Song Yi's best friend)
- When she was little. - Right.
Now I remember this place.
- You should come with Song Yi. - I remember.
- I'm sorry, but... - Why? I remember.
They didn't have this back then.
(9 years ago)
No. I remember this place now.
- But... - I just remember.
(Lie)
- Now I remember. - How do you remember it...
when it wasn't even here back then?
Why is this cave so deep?
(After passing through the memory-altering zone,)
I love how cool it is in here.
- It even has an arts center here. - How did they install all of this?
(they enter a noticeably darker area.)
Starting from here is the exclusive area...
- that's been closed for 114 years. - Really?
- For 114 years. - For 114 years?
This is a place that has never been revealed until now.
(A mysterious area that was hidden for over 100 years)
What is this?
(Following the light as if stepping into another dimension)
It feels like stepping into a mystical realm.
This is like "Interstellar."
There are raw ores here.
You're right.
(Exclaiming)
- Look. My goodness. - My goodness.
(A mining tunnel that still holds the original look of the mine)
- All of a sudden... - What is all this?
This is a mining tunnel where you can observe mineral ores.
This is amazing.
This is really fun.
- This was all made by human hands. - Yes.
(Where gold was mined 100 years ago)
They used to mine ores here.
The tunnel connects all the way over there.
(Transformed into a meditation space glowing with mystical light)
This is amazing.
It must have been just as cool here 500 years ago.
I want to climb up there and take a photo.
(Mesmerized by the sights,)
It makes you want to go up.
(they go deeper into the tunnel.)
Watch your head.
Haha will be fine, though.
What?
- We have guests. - Who are they?
- We have guests? - Who?
(Deep inside the cave,)
Hello.
(there are people?)
- Who are they? - You're here.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Three guests who have already explored the cave)
- What are you doing here? - Hello.
You're here.
Hello.
(Jung Eun Ji, the main vocalist of Apink)
- Who are they? - It's Eun Ji.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Lee Ju Yeon of After School)
Hello.
It's Ju Yeon.
(Actress Kim Ji Eun)
- We were having fun here. - It's Ji Eun.
- Ji Eun. - Hello.
(A powerhouse actor who embodies every role like a second skin...)
You punk!
Yes. I'm 22.
Tonight, legendary performances...
(and a versatile all-rounder who constantly exceeds expectations)
beyond your wildest imagination are waiting for you.
(She was on Running Man 4 years ago.)
- What's that? - Struck rich out of nowhere!
You don't know?
(Panting)
(Nouveau riche)
Dog Rich?
(Kim Ji Eun loaded with charms showed her delightfully goofy side.)
What are you doing?
- One of the five... - The five crazy singers.
(She showed up as 1 of the 5 crazy singers in K-pop 8 years ago.)
This is rock solid.
(The diva upgraded to the top 3 crazy singers.)
It's "Diva."
(Actress Lee Ju Yeon left a powerful impression...)
I've met countless people in my life.
(in the hit series "The Art of Sarah.")
How could you possibly know?
Eun Ji is back after a long time.
(On her latest visit,)
(she effortlessly defeated Jee Seok Sam...)
She's so strong.
(and demonstrated her strength as Female Kim Jong Kook.)
- How is she so strong? - Eun Ji.
(She's making a refreshing comeback with her 5th album, "Summer, I.")
- Hey, Eun Ji. - Hello.
(Long time no see!)
- Hi. - It's been a while.
- Hey. - How did you...
- Have some coffee. - All right.
(All food consumption in the cave was done with prior authorization.)
This is for you.
It's Ji Eun.
Ji Eun is dressed like a ghost. Is she a ghost today?
Have some coffee.
- Can we have it here? - Do you have mine?
(Frightened)
- Ji Eun, I didn't recognize you. - Is she a ghost?
- All right. - Coffee.
(Eyes gleaming)
Can we drink this here?
- We have coffee. - Hi.
(Hesitating)
- Hi. - Coffee?
- It's been a while. How are you? - Hello.
It feels like Ju Yeon poisoned this coffee.
- What? - Hello.
You didn't poison it, did you?
(From a ghost to a witch, are they guests for a horror special?)
Why would I poison it?
All right.
I bet those three did something together.
- A drama? - No.
- No. - You didn't?
Are you releasing a new album together?
(Not even close.)
- That's not it? - No.
Are the three of you doing something together?
This is my first time seeing them.
(What's more)
You haven't met before?
(Ju Yeon and Ji Eun meet for the first time.)
- We haven't met before. - It's our first time meeting.
- Really? - You haven't met before?
No, we haven't met before.
(Eun Ji)
I met her once when I hosted "Inkigayo."
Why are they here together today?
- We don't know. - Anyway, it's good to see...
(They have nothing in common,)
Ji Eun and Ju Yeon after such a long time.
(but it's still nice to see these three together.)
- That's right. - We should be grateful.
(Came by to enjoy the vacation together)
- Of course. - We should really be grateful.
- Right. - Thank you so much.
- Sure. - And Eun Ji released a solo album.
- A solo album. - Yes!
(Eun Ji is back with a solo album.)
- Really? - It's a new album.
- No way. - I'd love to hear her new song.
- Her song? - I took part...
in producing every song on this album.
- No way. - Is it an album?
- Yes. - An album?
(Sneakily)
- Unbelievable. - It'll sound even better in a cave.
- In a cave? - Can you actually sing for us?
(Instantly)
- She's such a talented vocalist. - Can you sing for us here?
- No way. - Exactly. She's so good.
(Eun Ji, a powerhouse vocalist who sings anywhere, anytime)
Your voice will sound amazing here.
- All right. - Eun Ji...
- No instrumental accompaniment. - No instrumental accompaniment?
- Really? - I'll sing a short snippet for you.
(A cappella cave performance)
Since we're in a cave, I'll sing it a cappella.
(Singing "i love LOVE," the title song, a cappella)
- I love it. - Nice.
You can really hear the cave's natural reverb.
- Exactly. - No way.
(Amazed)
(Master vocalist Eun Ji's powerful voice...)
- No way. - I can't believe it.
(fills the entire cave.)
That was insane.
I got goosebumps.
I love, love, love
(Still immersed in the song)
- Can you sing something else? - I love, love, love
How about singing an old favorite of ours?
(The uncle fan requests an encore.)
- No way. - That was amazing.
(All right.)
What else should I sing?
Our town where the brightest star shines
(She immediately sings "Hopefully Sky.")
(Cheering)
That's it.
In spring, when flowers bloom under the warm sunshine
(Amazed)
I bring you comfort, I bring you love
(A masterful performance elevated by the cave's natural reverb)
Through a song made just for you
(A blessing for the ears)
- Nice. - That was amazing.
(Moved)
- Eun Ji, you're so good. - That was incredible.
(Eun Ji's incredible vocals don't need any fancy equipment.)
- No way. - You're amazing.
Let's hear them sing "Aqua."
- "Aqua?" - What's wrong with you?
Why are you trying to humiliate us?
(A recommendation made purely to tease her)
- What's your problem? - Why...
are you trying to humiliate her?
Do you want your gums to collapse?
(Her vocal delivery is as good as any.)
Gums to collapse?
Seriously.
The other two aren't here to promote anything.
(Moving on to updates on Ju Yeon and Ji Eun)
That's right.
- I... - It's been eight years for Ju Yeon.
(On the show after 8 years and 4 years)
- Yes? Why am I here? - It's been so long.
- It's been eight years. - Eight years?
- And four for me. - I couldn't be more grateful.
- That's right. - We last saw her eight years ago.
Didn't Ju Yeon have a romance going on...
the last time she was here?
- Not at all. - With one of us?
(Ju Yeon's romantic pairing that the romance fan remembers?)
- I think she did. - That's how I remember it.
Were the socks yours?
(8 years ago, during the couple special)
- What is? - The socks.
(They picked items to pair up.)
I was going to choose the socks.
Really? Then why didn't you choose them?
I had a feeling they were his!
I'm also glad I wasn't paired up with you. Okay.
What's this? Is there romance blooming?
She and I? No way.
(They got caught up in a love-hate relationship.)
- We're close, that's all. - We're just friends.
After drinking together all day, this is how they'll part ways.
It was nice seeing you, Jung Chan Young.
She could've at least got my surname right.
(As same-agers, they were butting heads all day long.)
Who's Jung Chan Young? Who did you confuse him with?
- There was nothing like that. - Really?
(Reunited after 8 years)
Ju Yeon and... I see.
- Are you in love these days? - Is there someone?
- Love... - No, I'm not in love these days.
I've mentioned this before,
(The diva is on a romantic hiatus.)
but I used to prioritize...
- work over love. - Did that come first?
- In the past, right? - In the past.
But since about a year ago,
love has...
- Do you value love more now? - I want to be in love.
- Love comes before work now. - You're more desperate.
(Love has become more important than work to Ju Yeon.)
Meeting a decent man as soon as possible...
You want to meet someone.
- That'd be nice. - Do you know anyone?
- What about Se Chan? - How about him?
(Is romance in the air again after 8 years?)
- He's the only one who's single. - And he's decent.
(Flat-out rejecting)
- No way. - Why are you rejecting me?
- He's pretty decent. - He's a good man.
- Ju Yeon... - Anyone else?
Weren't you a K-pop idol?
- Of course. - It's golden then.
Don't. Just shut it.
(Met the requirements for now)
People will think I only date K-pop idols.
That's not true.
Are you an idol hunter?
- He doesn't actually hunt them. - Is he an idol hunter?
Word has it he's dated a lot of them.
I see. Yes, I heard that rumor too.
- Word has spread. - Forget it.
- But who? - I can't tell you that.
(Reporter Lee digs in deeper.)
I think I know who it was.
- You do? - Yes.
- How? - I know who you dated too.
Should I talk?
I know who you dated too. Should I talk?
(Exposing each other)
- Let's see who it hurts more. - Don't.
- I won't stand back and take it. - Why would you mention that?
Ju Yeon went silent all of a sudden.
It's better to leave it...
(Calm down.)
- to the imagination. - Exactly.
- That's enough, guys. - Let's keep quiet.
- We won't expose each other. - Sure.
Anyway, I'd like to thank Ju Yeon for appearing on the show...
(Reached a dramatic deal)
- Right. - after so long.
- It's been so long. - Isn't she here with Ji Eun...
for a horror special?
Are you sure you're not dressed as a ghost?
(A ghost)
- I'm not. - A ghost?
- Your face is too pale. - No way.
I'm dressed for a getaway.
- A getaway look? - For a vacation?
(All wrapped up)
- Your skin has always been pale. - Is that a getaway look?
- Ji Eun. - Like for a resort getaway, right?
That's right. A resort.
- Outside... - Have you always had pale skin?
(An anti-AC-chill outfit that sparked a misunderstanding)
- Yes, I'm on the paler side. - I see.
You should step outside every now and then.
(Worried)
Get some sun, will you?
(Diagnosed with a melanin deficiency)
- Got it. - You need vitamin D.
(What race awaits today, paired with one-of-a-kind summer outfits?)
Today's race is Beat the Heat With a Scratch Vacation.
- A Scratch Vacation? - Scratch?
- A Scratch Vacation? - What are we scratching?
- Remember what we got earlier? - As in credit cards?
(Vacation expense: 10 dollars)
After a fun summer getaway,
(Pays 1 dollar)
you'll pay as much of the price as you like.
(Pays 0 dollars)
- Oh, no. - What's this?
(Vacation expense: 7 dollars)
If the last payer gets stuck paying the most,
they get a chance...
to guess who paid the least.
(Point out)
Guess correctly,
and the lowest payer takes on the remaining balance.
(Pays 7 dollars, Payment waived)
The higher your total accumulated cost,
the greater your chances of a penalty.
You must try to keep...
- your amount low. - It's best to be in the middle.
- Right. - I see.
You'll now head out to win perks for the race.
- Okay. - Got it.
Ji Eun and even Ju Yeon...
Ju Yeon's no pushover.
(They head to where they'll play the next game.)
- What? - Aqua World?
- What's this? - Was this always here?
I wonder what it is this time.
(Amazed)
(This breathtaking place is...)
- What's this? - Is there a stage?
What is this place?
(a massive concert hall inside the cave.)
- What? - It's huge.
- It must be an auditorium. - What is this?
(A cultural arts space inside the cave,)
- What is this place? - They must hold live shows here.
(where visitors can enjoy stunning media art)
This must be an auditorium.
Performing here would be an acoustic paradise.
(Day job: Singer)
(You're right.)
- This place is incredible. - Perform "Aqua" for us.
- Aqua - Aqua
The sight of you makes me want to sneeze
("Ah-Choo?")
Aqua
The sight of you makes me want to sneeze
(Zero awkwardness)
They're similar.
Why are you standing in the middle?
Ji Eun has really fair skin.
- Exactly. - You're almost pale.
- Is it weird? - How long have you been indoors?
(She's a lot paler under bright light.)
I've been working on sets lately.
- Is this where you live? - You probably don't even tan.
(Her vampire complexion makes you think she lives in a cave.)
- Ji Eun, seriously. - She's so pale.
- Her skin is so fair. - She was probably born like that.
Who stays this pale in the summer?
- Exactly. It's the summer. - She's so pale.
She needs redder lips.
He's right. You should put some lipstick on.
- Should I? - Seok Jin, give her yours.
- This is bright red. - I have one.
- She has one of her own. - Do you?
Here. I have a red lip balm.
This will make your lips pop.
(Seok Jin's wife's lip balm turns dark lips into cherry-red lips.)
- This is his wife's. - Exactly. We know.
(Smiling)
It's nice to give your lips some color.
The game you'll play here...
(The first mission, with payment perks on the line)
is Diva in the Dark.
(Mission 1 of Beat the Heat With a Scratch Vacation)
You'll be playing in two teams.
- What's the game? - Diva?
One player from each team will dance blindfolded...
to find the colored sticker.
- When the music pauses, - Those over there.
you must have at least one foot...
- on the sticker to pass. - But how?
(Success)
The winning team gets ten points,
(10 points)
while the best dancer...
earns five.
(5 points)
While blindfolded.
After four rounds,
the team with the highest score wins.
Three players on the winning team will be exempt from paying.
- What? - No way.
- Exempt? - Nice.
- We have to win this. - We chose your teams for you.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Haha,
Ye Eun, and Ju Yeon are a team.
Ju Yeon too?
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Se Chan,
Eun Ji, and Ji Eun are a team.
- Okay. - Nice.
Eun Ji's one of...
- the best dancers. - Please don't say that.
I haven't really gotten along well with dancing.
- I see. - But you're in a girl group.
- Ju Yeon's a great dancer. - She was in a girl group.
Ye Eun's a decent dancer too.
(Former idol, former dance club member)
- Really? - Yes, she's incredible.
Round One will be...
(Round One)
Se Chan versus Ye Eun.
(Round 1: Dongducheon Dancer versus Eight-Foot Tall Ghost)
- Wait. Me versus her? - With Se Chan?
- It's a 1-on-1 game. - That's right.
(Rule: Reach the numbered square diagonally to win)
Is it a 1-on-1 game?
- This doesn't look easy. Seriously. - Aqua
Do we have to walk there while dancing?
- I should warm up. - I knew it. Look at Ddochi dance.
- Look at Ddochi dance. - Nice.
(Dancing)
(The Eight-Foot Tall Ghost shows off her new moves.)
You look like an octopus.
(Nervous)
- She's so good. - Doesn't she have any bones?
Play the song.
("Touch my body" by SISTAR)
Oh, this song.
(Go!)
(The key move is swaying to the music.)
(Here are 2 drunkards.)
Nice going!
(Bring it.)
(Nice!)
- Nice going! - She's so good.
- What do I do? - She's adorable.
(Feeling the pressure)
(Moving forward with her shirt flapping)
- Nice! - There you go.
She's so good.
(Lost in the music)
- Nice going. - That's it.
(The audience is satisfied.)
Nice going.
(Getting in the way)
(In the midst of it all, they've moved close to the numbers.)
Where is she?
(Se Chan is in the numbered square!)
- Nice! You're doing great. - No way.
She learned how to dance.
(Se Chan will win if he stays where he is.)
She's so good at it now.
- Five, four, - No way.
- three, two, one. - What?
- Time's up. - No way.
(The music stops.)
- Seriously? - Are you kidding me?
- No way. - Could you see where you were?
- Please take off your blindfolds. - What?
(Who finished inside the numbered square?)
- How is this possible? - No way.
- Ye Eun wins. - Yes!
- No way. - My gosh.
- What on earth? - What was that?
- How did you do that? - No way. Good job!
(What happened in that short amount of time?)
(Ssaebssaeb was doing the twist on the number.)
- Nice going. - Good job.
She learned how to dance. She's so good at it now.
(He stepped off it as he continued to dance.)
Where are you going?
(Ddochi made it to the exact spot right before time ran out.)
One. Time's up.
- Ddochi, what's gotten into you? - Wasn't I amazing?
(The Eight-Foot Tall Ghost comes alive...)
(whenever there's a dance floor.)
- I can't believe it. - Do this move for everyone.
(Of course!)
Ye Eun also scores five points for her dancing.
(Ddochi even earned 5 points for her dancing!)
- No way. - Both her feet were in the square.
Se Chan's dancing wasn't that bad.
- I couldn't see a thing. - But hers was better.
(No!)
- Really? - Jong Kook, come up.
Ddochi did this move right here.
(Feeling proud)
Ddochi, nicely done.
(Bitter)
(Team Jong Kook: 0, Team Jae Seok: 15)
That exceeded all my expectations.
- Really? - Ddochi, nice.
(Ddochi earned 15 points all alone!)
- I can't believe it. - Nicely done.
- How did you make it in there? - I couldn't see a thing.
(Hyper)
I swear, I couldn't see a thing.
(Round One ended with Ji Ye Eun's overwhelming victory.)
You can't see a thing.
- The next round... - Yes?
(Revealing the dancers of Round Two)
- This is tough. - is between Eun Ji and Ju Yeon.
(Round 2: Eun Ji versus Ju Yeon)
- Yes! - Go get it!
It's the battle of the girl groups!
It's After School versus Apink.
(Girl Group Showdown, After School versus Apink)
After School versus Apink.
Both group names start with A.
(Korea's Pussycat Dolls known for their powerful performances)
(After School graduate Lee Ju Yeon)
(The pure, innocent girl group that debuted 15 years ago)
(Apink's lead vocalist Jung Eun Ji)
Ju Yeon is number 1, and Eun Ji is number 2.
(A showdown between 2nd-generation girl group senior and junior)
- You can do this. - Play the song.
("Super Star" by Jewelry)
(Ju Yeon makes a head start.)
What's happening?
(Raise)
Hands up.
(Crazy)
What... What moves are they?
(Her motions are very intuitive.)
Isn't this the correct move?
(Drunk on the vibes)
She's dancing weirdly.
What is that?
(What's that?)
(Deeply engrossed)
(She instinctively made her way to the camera zone.)
What is going on? What is Ju Yeon...
- Where do I go? - What's up with her?
Where is she going?
- Where are you going? - What are you doing, Ju Yeon?
(Back on stage after a long time, she's completely in her element.)
Hey, Ju Yeon!
(The superstar look)
(Cheering)
She owns the stage.
(Meanwhile, she's shaking her body.)
Nice moves.
She's just enjoying herself.
(While she's lost in the groove,)
Ju Yeon is just...
Look at her.
(Eun Ji is getting closer to the target!)
She owns the stage.
- Where do I go? - Nice moves.
- She's almost there. - Where am I?
- A bit more. - Slowly. A bit more.
- Five, four, three, - Stop!
(She dances her way toward the voice.)
- two, one, stop. - Stay there!
(The music ends.)
That's incredible.
(Eun Ji who found the square marker wins!)
Jung Eun Ji won.
Well done!
- Good job. - She nailed it.
(Team Jong Kook 10, Team Jae Seok 15)
(Eunji, the human compass)
You danced so well.
- Your moves. - Very well done.
Where am I?
(She's hoarse.)
(She's way too far.)
- Ju Yeon, you... - How come...
- What was that? - What did you do?
She gave in.
What was that, Ju Yeon? You were over here.
(Angry)
That was weird.
(Embarrassed)
Ju Yeon. You were meant to go that way.
(She just danced as much as she wanted.)
Well...
- Guys, listen. - That's the good spot.
This person has an advantage because they can hear them.
- Haha, that's... - You're right.
- I don't know a thing. - You don't, do you?
- Let's swap seats. - You...
(They want to move to a spot where they can guide her by voice.)
- We should swap. - It's confusing.
- They give audible hints. - It's confusing.
- Come over here. - Swap seats.
- Swap seats. - Okay.
(They agree to switch seats.)
You don't hear a thing.
- Okay? - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
- By the way, Jong Kook... - Yes?
You've mellowed.
- The old Jong Kook... - What?
- would've thrown a fit. - I mean...
- The thing is, - Back in the day...
(The newlywed groom is not as fiery as he used to be.)
you had a good point.
- You're not you. - You're wrong.
- Why are you so nice? - You had a point.
What did I do?
- What did you do, really? - What was that, Ju Yeon?
I danced hard, but the song...
Honestly...
- The song was too... - Gosh.
(The 2nd-generation diva tried her best, though.)
Ju Yeon lost us ten points.
(Team Jae Seok only earned 5 points for the dance in the next round.)
- I danced weird and lost. - Yes.
- Was it that bad? - It was a total mess, Ju Yeon.
Two from each team will compete this last time.
- Two each? - Two versus two?
(Round 4: Jae Seok and Seok Jin versus Ji Hyo and Jong Kook)
Jae Seok and Seok Jin versus Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
- Okay. - Sounds good.
Even if you go straight ahead, you can't tell where your right is.
(Discussing strategy before the final round)
Because you're blindfolded.
Jong Kook, when you're dancing,
if you go to the right, I'll go "hey."
- As a sign? - "Hey."
- "Hey?" - "Hey" for "right."
- If I say "ai," that's left. - Good luck.
"Hey" means "right."
(Ssaebssaeb can't play games without tricks.)
- "Ai" means "left." - Okay.
They plotted.
- Ready? - Jong Kook.
- Count for me. - Okay.
("Twist King" by Turbo)
Let's go!
Hey.
(Kim Turbo is excited to dance to his song.)
Hey!
What is this?
(Grooving)
Twist!
Wait.
- Stop the music. - Why?
- Come on. - I was having fun.
Why do you play Turbo songs whenever it's Jong Kook's turn?
I'm a Turbo member.
Play something else.
Why can't they play Turbo when I am Turbo?
(He's been listening to his songs for 16 years,)
(but he suddenly starts nitpicking.)
I want to have some fun too.
(A song request)
CORTIS' "REDRED."
- CORTIS. - Let's start over.
(He requests a new song, thinking Turbo received special treatment.)
- "REDRED." - "REDRED."
I was having fun just then.
- We should start over. - What's "Red?"
- What's "Red?" - What is "Red?"
- Recent songs... - They don't know.
- I don't know new songs either. - "What's 'Red?'"
I'll dance "Twist King" anyway.
- Whose "Red?" - Ready?
Play the song.
("REDRED" by CORTIS)
That's it.
Let's go!
(The two men get it started.)
- What's this? - This is it.
- I'm going the right way. - Seok Jin!
It's this way.
(Pretty good!)
(Jae Seok's choreo is pretty decent.)
(The others are dancing like an old lady.)
(Clashing)
Who are you?
I think this is the right way.
(A mid-level manager dancing among his subordinates)
Keep going.
Forward. Jong Kook, go forward!
Jong Kook, go forward!
- Jong Kook, go forward! - Go forward!
(Too focused on dancing to hear him)
- Forward! - Jong Kook, go forward!
- Which way? - It's not that way.
(He starts cheating too.)
Back. Go back.
(Both teams are now blatantly shouting out instructions.)
- Stop right there. - Okay, a bit more.
- A bit more. - Four,
(Did anyone hear them correctly?)
- A bit more. Go backward. - three, two,
- Not there. - one, stop!
(The music ends.)
- Remove your blindfolds. - Okay!
Ji Hyo was almost there.
- Okay! - Ji Hyo!
(Seok Sam steps on the number.)
- Okay! - Seok Jin and Jae Seok won.
(Team Jong Kook: 10, Team Jae Seok: 30)
- Okay. - Well done.
- Okay! - Well done.
(Team Jae Seok wins the game.)
- We won? - Okay!
- What was that? - We were close.
- Okay! - You didn't coach me.
- I did. - He shouted like crazy.
- He did? - "Forward."
(I shouted like this.)
"Jong Kook, go forward."
- "Go forward." - We all chanted.
(Manager Kim couldn't hear it and gets mad at him.)
- We all joined in. - "Go, forward."
(Disappointed)
- The match is over. - Okay.
- Ju Yeon... - Ju Yeon and Eun Ji.
- Yes, Ju Yeon and Eun Ji. - "Catch Catch."
I don't know "Catch Catch" well.
(Right after Round 2, the girl group showdown)
They said they'd play "Catch Catch."
- I was learning the moves. - Were you?
You suddenly...
(Ju Yeon said she learned the choreo to "Catch Catch.")
You should've played "Catch Catch."
- Eun Ji's great at this. - Honestly,
(A bonus round of "Catch Catch" has been arranged!)
I don't know it,
- but I'll do my best. - You can do it!
(Eun Ji)
Crush your senior with your new moves.
(Annoyed)
- What "new moves?" - I don't care.
(A big match for pride, not points)
- I'll go for it. I'm strong. - Ju Yeon doesn't know new songs.
Watch out.
(Will she be able to show what she's got for real?)
I'm scared.
- Play the song. - What now?
("Catch Catch" by Choi Ye Na)
(Starting with the key dance move)
(Moving the same arm and leg instead of alternating)
(Flustered)
This is insane.
(She said she was confident.)
- What... What's going on? - What is this?
Eun Ji, you're doing great!
(Eun Ji is dancing as if she's breaking bricks.)
- What are you doing? - What is this?
- Eun Ji, keep going. You're there! - Ju Yeon's...
(She found the jib camera perfectly!)
I think she's just...
(The visual center's expertise)
Will you pause?
- Wait. Ju Yeon. - We won. Nice!
(The music stops.)
Nice.
You said you practiced "Catch Catch."
(Laughing out loud)
- What's wrong? - Eun Ji aced it.
This is how it goes.
(Catch)
Dance without the blindfold.
How did I do?
(I think I did a good job.)
It won't do. Dance without the blindfold.
You danced "Gangnam Style."
(Giddy-up)
Isn't this it?
I thought you were dancing to "Gangnam Style."
(A nostalgic performance by a 2nd-gen diva...)
It was more like "Gangnam Style."
- Gosh. - You danced a lot.
(brings the bonus match to an end.)
Team Jae Seok won. You can exclude three members.
Now we'll pay.
(The 7 of them will pay.)
The first vacation spot was Gwangmyeong Cave.
The total amount is 184 dollars.
- The entrance fee. - The entrance fee is 100 dollars.
- The coffee too? - Cave bread, 30 dollars.
The coffee cost 54 dollars.
(Total: 184 dollars)
The remaining seven members must cover the bill.
(This amount will be split among 7 people.)
- Okay. - You pay however much you want,
(6 people will pay in order, choosing how much they want to pay.)
and the last person must pay the remaining balance.
Let's split it fairly. It's not that much.
(If they can find the lowest payer, they'll be exempt from paying.)
We can split it evenly.
I have no idea what that means.
The last person will have to pay the most.
(Calmly explaining again)
- Yes. - That person...
names whoever they think paid the least,
(Thinking)
and if they're right, the person they named...
(Anyone can tell she doesn't get it.)
must cover the rest.
(Fake nod)
Hang on.
Give me paper and a pen.
Are you giving her a special tutorial?
(Mr. Yu has to teach her 1-on-1.)
I must give a special tutorial.
I've never had a guest like her.
(Embarrassed)
You really don't get it yet?
- Ju Yeon, you... - Look, Ju Yeon.
You didn't watch Running Man?
- The bill is 180 dollars. - It's so confusing.
- Listen. - Pretend it's 180 dollars.
- We must split that between us. - Yes.
(They'll pay in order. It's as simple as that.)
- There are five on our team. - Yes.
(Super focused)
Oh, okay. I get it now.
(Unbelievable)
(Her lesson is over, and they'll choose 3 people to pay.)
- It's her first time. Be nice. - Okay.
- It's teamwork. - Be nice.
(They simply play rock-paper-scissors.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do this.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Ye Eun and Haha lost.)
Okay.
(Payment: Haha, Ye Eun, Exempt: Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Ju Yeon)
This isn't right.
Right now...
- I don't think... - Go over there.
- Go on. - We won.
(Team Jong Kook in the meantime)
- You pick the order. - The minimum...
Let's pay 25 dollars each.
- Twenty-five each. - Okay.
(They promise to pay 25 dollars each.)
Or you pick who you think paid the least.
He can do that. Let's give that a try.
(The 25-Dollar Alliance is formed to avoid paying the least.)
- Seriously. - Let's do it.
Okay. Let's do that.
(He's in charge of searching.)
I go last? I can do that. I can manage.
- Se Chan. - I'll go last.
(Payment Order)
You know the rules. We won.
- It's those two. - Haha, you're up first.
(Haha will go 1st and choose the amount he wants.)
- Go and swipe. - We agreed on an amount.
- Play fair. - Of course.
(How much will he pay out of the 184 dollars?)
- I'll play fair but confusing. - Of course.
Of the 184 dollars spent in the cave,
(If they get caught paying the lowest amount,)
how much will you pay?
(they'll have to pay big.)
Write down how much you'll pay.
One...
I don't want to spend even a dollar.
(Shouting)
A dollar and 35 cents.
(1.35 dollars)
(Out of 184 dollars, he pays just 1.35 dollars.)
I must pay this much. I have no choice.
(Will someone pay even less than him?)
It has to be. It's not an easy call.
(Ye Eun is up next.)
It's not easy.
(Amount paid: Haha 1.34 cents)
(She pays 7.7 dollars.)
There's no accumulated total.
(The turn of the head of the 25-Dollar Alliance)
(He pays 25 dollars as promised.)
We made a deal for the first round, so I'll give it a go.
If this doesn't work, then it becomes war.
I paid the amount we agreed on, which is 25 dollars.
Hello.
(Ji Eun, his ally, enters the booth.)
Write down the amount you want to pay.
(Will Ji Eun pay 25 dollars as agreed?)
(50 cents)
The minimum... Let's pay 25 dollars each.
(When Jong Kook suggested the 25-Dollar Alliance,)
- Shall we? Okay. - Seriously.
(she agreed wholeheartedly.)
Let's do that.
(Ji Eun betrayed them immediately.)
- Take it with you. - I take it?
- Keep it with you. - What if they see it?
Shoot.
I was quick, wasn't I?
Yes, Ji Eun.
- I wrote the amount right away. - You wrote it right away?
(The lowest spender so far is shamelessly coming back.)
- How much did you write? - The amount we promised.
- You wrote 3.3 dollars? - No.
(Ji Hyo and Eun Ji from the 25-Dollar Alliance also pay.)
Is it 184 dollars?
(Finally, Se Chan enters.)
Do I check this?
(Se Chan has to pay the entire remaining balance.)
Of the 184 dollars spent in the cave,
(How much is left from the 184 dollars after everyone has paid?)
- the amount left for you to pay... - The amount I should spend?
- is 144.44 dollars. - What?
What?
- It's 144.44 dollars. - It's 144...
(Pausing)
(Unbelievable)
It's 144.4...
It's 144.44 dollars?
You may leave now.
(Exclaiming)
This is fun.
- Well... - Why?
Come here.
- How much is it? - I...
- This is Gwangmyeong, right? - Yes.
You've turned me into the Gwangmyeong Gangster.
(Pretending not to know)
- Why? - It's really...
- These sneaky people. - Oh, come on.
(Yang Ssaebssaeb lost it when he saw the unexpected balance.)
- The balance is like 50 dollars. - It's really unfair.
- Fifty dollars? - How much was left?
- Really? - The amount...
Se Chan has to pay...
- You guys are really mean. - is 144.44 dollars.
- What? - Hold on!
- It's 144 dollars? - Hold on.
(I'll find out who paid the lowest amount.)
- I'll find out who it is. - Hold on.
This is too much, Jong Kook.
(Feeling betrayed)
- Eun Ji... - One hundred and forty dollars?
(50 cents)
- and Ji Eun... - It wasn't me.
You didn't pay.
- She didn't pay. - We'll reveal...
the amount paid by the person who paid the least.
The person who paid the least...
- paid one cent. - One cent?
- One cent. - One cent?
(One of them paid 1 cent.)
- One cent... - Could you pay just one cent?
(1.35 dollars, 7.7 dollars, 25 dollars)
They paid just one cent?
(50 cents)
The card fee would cost more.
(There are only 2 suspects left.)
- Really? - One cent?
(Who had the guts to pay 1 cent? Eun Ji or Ji Hyo?)
- Who paid one cent? - That's amazing.
That was you, right?
- That was you, right? - Seriously.
(If Se Chan finds the culprit, he can turn the tables.)
I need to find who paid one cent.
They didn't pay.
Paying one cent was just really rude.
How could you pay one cent?
I'm really not that bad.
(She paid 50 cents.)
(Laughing)
I paid.
It's not Haha.
Eun Ji is acting weird too.
Eun Ji, you're also... You came out too late.
- Right. - Her reaction is really weird.
(Suspect 1: Eun Ji who looked awkward after revealing the amount)
- She erased one zero. - So...
(Staring)
- Her reaction is a bit... - I didn't erase one zero.
I didn't pay the amount I agreed on.
(Suspect 2: Ji Hyo who felt guilty first)
That's right. I didn't pay the amount I agreed on.
I didn't pay the amount I agreed on.
(Staring)
In my opinion...
- It's... - Could you pick one person?
- But... - Between Eun Ji and Ji Hyo.
It's not easy for a guest to pay one cent.
(A clear answer)
(Detective Yu has got a strong theory.)
It's not easy for a guest...
- to pay one cent. - That's right.
(Certain)
It's Ji Hyo. Song Ji Hyo.
If it wasn't a member,
the person wouldn't pay just one cent.
Do you think Ji Hyo paid one cent?
(Could Ji Hyo be the one who paid 1 cent, just as Detective Yu says?)
There could be a twist.
(The final chance to choose the culprit)
Please pick the person.
- I pick... - Hold on.
Se Chan.
(Come on.)
- The energy of Gwangmyeong Cave! - Hey.
Don't pick the person you want it to be.
(He has to find the one who paid 1 cent to make them pay.)
Think rationally.
Will you pick one of the members?
One, two...
(Shouting)
Hey!
(He's drawing power from the cave.)
Maybe it's Haha.
It could be Jong Kook.
It really isn't me.
- I pick... - You know me.
(Who betrayed Se Chan by paying 1 cent?)
- Ji Hyo? - Hold on.
- Song Ji Hyo. - Song Ji Hyo.
You picked Song Ji Hyo.
- I think it'll be Song Ji Hyo. - Hold on.
I get the feeling Ji Hyo paid one cent.
No way.
Did Song Ji Hyo...
pay one cent?
She did.
- She did. - Yes!
(Se Chan caught the culprit.)
It was 144.44...
- My blood pressure is rising. - That one cent...
The deity of this cave!
- It felt like Ji Hyo's work. - I'm no longer a gangster.
I'm an innocent citizen.
Paying one cent felt like something Ji Hyo would have done.
(Ji Hyo, who paid 1 cent, is caught by Detective Yu.)
I feel dizzy.
That one cent and Ji Hyo...
For Eun Ji to pay one cent...
(Paid 5 dollars)
- That's too... - Guests don't pay one cent.
I had a feeling it was Ji Hyo.
Se Chan succeeded in identifying the culprit.
- You will pay zero dollars. - Why?
I could see the determined look on Ji Hyo's face before she left.
(Ji Hyo, who paid 1 cent to save money and got caught,)
And that one cent felt like Ji Hyo's work.
Will Ji Hyo pay the entire amount?
(has to take over Se Chan's 144.44-dollar share...)
- She'll pay the entire amount. - I wrote zero dollars at first,
- then I changed it to one cent. - Song Ji Hyo...
will pay 144.45 dollars.
- Okay. - Ji Hyo.
(and pay 144.45 dollars.)
I'd have to be more thorough next time.
So I wouldn't get caught.
(They head to the next destination after paying.)
I really thought you didn't pay anything.
- Ji Hyo... - Yes?
has been feeling really down after the one cent incident.
Me? That's not true.
- I... - In my opinion,
no matter how little...
- Ji Eun and Eun Ji paid, - Right.
(Detective Yu's deduction is frighteningly accurate.)
- Not 1 cent. - they wouldn't have paid 1 cent.
- That amount... - Right.
(No one will be paying 1 cent next time.)
It's not an amount a guest would pay.
- Also... - That's right.
Why did you do that?
(Glancing)
Seok Jin.
I'm going to lean my seat back a bit. I'm sorry.
No.
(The amusement park for Prankster Yu is open.)
It's an amusement park ride.
- That looks fun. - Hey.
- Jae Seok... - Why are you lying down?
Your senior could lie down a bit.
Let me lean it back a bit.
Forget about that.
It's touching my knees.
Are you all right?
(There's enough space.)
It's touching his knees.
- Come on. - This much is fine.
Please have some manners.
(After Jee-rasoni's hard battle for his permanent seat...)
- It's annoying. - Be respectful.
Pull it forward.
We're on our way to lunch.
- Yes. - Right.
(The next vacation spot is revealed.)
We're going to eat by the stream...
(A restaurant near the refreshing mountain stream)
- so you could enjoy the vacation. - We're going to a stream?
Really?
We're going to a place where you can eat baeksuk and meat.
(Rejuvenating baeksuk...)
Baeksuk by a stream sounds amazing.
(and pork belly are waiting.)
- That sounds nice. - Summer calls for pork belly.
We'll give you a chance to make up for the payment...
(A quick quiz to make up for the payment)
- on the way. - Nice.
We'll play You Don't Know This?
In a dialect.
Are you fine with speaking in a dialect?
(Imitating the producer's accent)
- Eun Ji. - That's not quite right.
You're from Busan, right?
- I'll get them all right. - These days,
there's a dialect quiz going around on social media...
that 99 percent of people in Seoul get wrong.
You'll listen to Eun Ji, who's from Busan,
(They have to guess the meaning of Eun Ji's Busan dialect to win.)
speak in the Busan dialect...
and guess the meaning. If you get it right,
- Okay. - five dollars will be deducted.
- Nice. - Nice.
- Haha should know the answer. - I would.
(A project to catch the guy who acts like he's from Busan)
- He's... - My hometown is...
- Do I have to do it too? - also nearby.
Do I have to do it too?
(Of course)
Yes, you should.
- You... - Hold on.
Eun Ji, what do you think about his dialect?
His is fake.
- Do I really have to do this? - His is fake, right?
- A fake. - His is really fake.
- Fake. - Fake.
Do you all want to get hit?
If Eun Ji reads...
- the questions well, - Yes?
she'll get five dollars deducted as well.
- Nice. - Nice.
- We shouldn't look. - My worry is...
- that Ju Yeon... - Okay.
just understood the rules here.
Do you understand the rule, Ju Yeon?
I understood.
(All right)
- You did? - You just need to know the dialect.
I'm not really good at understanding the dialect.
We're doing this because we don't know the dialect.
(That's the point.)
Here's the first question.
(The first dialect quiz)
"Gagan aga gaga?"
Let me answer!
- Is he the child... - "Ga?"
- he gave birth to? - Let me answer.
- Incorrect. - Is he the child of that person?
- Incorrect. - Could you say that again?
(Incorrect)
(It's too hard. Please say it one more time.)
- I'll read it one more time. - Loudly.
"Gagan aga gaga."
- Let me answer! - Yes?
That child...
- "He is..." - is a baby...
- So is he a child? - Let me answer!
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
- It's hard. - Is that child...
the child who left?
(Tilting the chair)
(He put up with his prank, but he got it wrong.)
- It's over. - The child who left.
- Let me answer! - The child...
- It's over. - That...
Is he...
- the person you know? - Let me answer.
(Incorrect)
- Please say it again. - The most...
important word here...
is "gagan."
(The point is gagan.)
- Gagwan? - Gagan.
- Gagan. - Gagan.
- "Gagan aga gaga?" - "Gagan."
- Let me answer! - Jae Seok.
Is that the place...
- that child went? - Incorrect!
- Wait. Are you really from Busan? - The context.
- There's a context. - Just tell us the context.
- The context... - Where in Busan did you live?
- I lived in Haeundae-gu in Busan. - The context...
- I couldn't say it any clearer. - Okay.
(Feeling frustrated, Eun Ji gives them the last hint.)
- Is that right? - I'll say it.
- Say it. - What's the situation?
- The situation... - The situation.
- Give us a hint. - "Gagan aga..."
(A gesture hint has been added.)
"Gagan aga gaga?"
(Rummaging)
- Give us a hint. - "Gagan aga..."
"Gagan aga gaga?"
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
I got it.
- Is that the child who paid? - Incorrect.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
Is my belly really this big?
(Incorrect)
Let me answer!
Is he the one who took it?
That's correct.
(Trying to lean back)
(Seok Sam gets the answer right despite Prankster Yu's distraction.)
That's correct.
- That's right. - "Gagan aga..."
- My belonging is gone. - Someone took it.
(5 dollars has been deducted from his bill.)
Is he the one who took it?
(He finally knows what "gagan" means now.)
- "Gagan?" - "Gagan!"
- The person who took it. - Is he the one who took it?
(Blinking)
I'm also from South Gyeongnam Province.
- What happened, Haha? - Well...
We...
- Our people say "gajyeogan." - Aren't you from Busan?
The child who took it...
(The self-proclaimed Busan native makes a lame excuse.)
- "Gagan." - "Gagan."
I get it now. She's really from Busan.
Be quiet! You punk.
Should we...
go head-to-head today?
- Sure. - Or...
(Go ahead.)
Let's do that, you punk.
Oh, no. Here's the second question.
(She gives the second question to protect the players.)
- The second one. - Okay.
"Son jjallina?"
- What? - "Son..."
- "Son jjallina?" - "Son jjallina?"
(Confused)
- Getting cut? - Let me answer.
- Are your hands small? - Incorrect.
- Let me answer. - "Son jjallina?"
- Are you scared? - Incorrect.
(Incorrect)
Let me answer. Who do you think you're fooling?
- Let me answer. - "Son jjallina?"
- Is that really so bothersome? - Incorrect.
(Incorrect)
- "Son jjallina?" - "Son jjallina?"
(The fake Busan native got it wrong again.)
"Son jjallina?"
- Watch... - Look.
Watch my eyes carefully.
- Let me answer! - Let me answer.
Yes, Jae Seok.
- Do your hands reach? - No way.
- That's correct. - Okay.
- "Son jjallina?" - That's right.
- Are your hands small? - This is...
almost like "honjaobseoye."
(It's hard.)
- It's so hard. - It's so hard.
(5 dollar has been deducted from Jae Seok's bill.)
You should know this much.
It's so hard.
Would people understand us...
if we say that in Busan?
They would. They all know it.
Eun Ji...
(Slandering)
doesn't seem to be from Haeundae.
She seems to be from Yangsan.
(The fake Busan native is rambling again.)
- I'm from Busan. - Right?
I'm a Busan native.
- Where is that place? - Can you reach it?
- Mister. - This is fun.
- Can you reach it? - Where is that place?
- Let's carry on. - You're a fake.
I'm the ambassador for Haeundae.
- Hey! - No way.
I'm the ambassador.
I'll be waiting to be Haeundae's next ambassador.
(He's in danger of losing his Haeundae ambassador title.)
Eun Ji would be the right person for it.
Let's carry on.
- It's the 3rd question. - The 3rd question.
(Would Haha be able to get it right this time?)
- "Ni waire ebitno?" - Let me answer!
Why did you get so skinny?
"Ebitno." Right.
(Correct)
I know "ebitno."
Why did you get thinner?
(He belatedly pretends to know.)
- "Ebitna?" - It's so hard.
I couldn't say "Let me answer" quick enough.
My grandma used to say that all the time.
- Why did you get so skinny? - You heard that?
(It's amazing that there was a time when he was skinny.)
- Mister. - Why did you get so skinny?
Mister.
(A long face)
- Here's the next one. - Okay.
"Aga wagure kkaelbatno?"
What? "Kkaelbatno?"
- "Kkaelbatno?" - "Kkaelbatno?"
- Why is he so annoying? - Incorrect.
Why does that person make me so annoyed?
(Incorrect)
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
Why is he being so hyper?
(Incorrect)
- Incorrect. - It's not correct?
Why is he so weak?
- Sorry? - Why is he so weak?
(Incorrect)
- Weak? Incorrect. - Here.
- Haha, don't you know what it is? - He's clueless.
- He doesn't know. - Don't you know this?
- That's what I said. - I mean...
Okay, focus.
(He's putting his Busan pride on the line.)
- Should I try to answer? - Sure, go ahead.
Why is he so feeble?
- Incorrect. - He's clueless!
(Incorrect)
- He's absolutely clueless. - No way.
(He's about to be stripped of his honorary Busan status.)
- What a fake. - Exactly.
- When did they change the meaning? - Unbelievable.
- What's up, Mr. Haeundae? - It's like this.
(Drinking water from a bottle)
Here's the gist of it.
You get like this in the summer.
(Hinting with her body language)
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
Why's he sprawled out like that, being so lazy?
(Correct)
- That is correct. - Yes!
(Haeundae Ambassador barely got it right.)
It's finally coming back to me.
- He didn't understand the dialect. - I get it now.
- That's right. - He got it thanks to the hint.
What are you talking about? Want to get slapped?
Bring it, you brat.
(While the wannabe Busaner is spared from last place)
- Isn't this the last one? - Yes, here's the last one.
(There's only one question left.)
- Only the Seoulites remain. - This is tough.
(Only 5 people from the Seoul metropolitan area...)
It's just between us Seoulites.
(remain for the final round.)
Here's the last one.
- Juri bada onna. - What?
Juri bada onna.
Let me answer. Fetch it together.
(Incorrect)
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
Could you officiate our wedding?
(Incorrect)
Don't you know what "juri" means?
- Get the rope. - Incorrect.
Go and get it.
- Incorrect. - What are we supposed to get?
Do I need to help out?
(Smug)
- Let's turn to Haha. - Let me answer. Get water.
(Does the fake Busan native know the answer?)
- Haha, give them a clue. - Give a hint using body language.
Here. Juri bada onna.
- What on earth? - What?
(Money gesture)
- Are you kidding me? - Let me answer. Settle the tab.
(He figured it's about money.)
- What? Incorrect. - Let me answer. Apply for a loan.
(Incorrect)
Let me answer. Don't forget the change.
That is correct.
(Correct)
(Lastly, 5 dollars have been deducted from Ddochi's bill.)
- Right? - See? I knew what it was.
- Juri bada onna. - That is correct.
(Haha's clue was actually spot on.)
Right?
- See? I knew what it was. - Really?
- Juri bada onna. - This is what I did.
(Smug)
- But that... - I thought it was this.
- Juri, I see. - See?
Don't forget the change.
(The result of the dialect quiz)
- What a bummer. - I was clueless.
- I had no idea. - Juri bada onna.
(5-dollar deduction: Seok Jin, Jae Seok, Jong Kook, Haha, Ye Eun,)
Ye Eun also got to deduct five dollars,
and Eun Ji did too for hosting the quiz.
(and Eun Ji)
- Thank you. - All right.
(After a fun side trip to Busan)
- I'm at zero dollars anyway. - Nice.
- Where are we headed? - This road leads to Anyang.
- What? - You're right. Anyang Station.
- Straight ahead... - It's Anyang up ahead.
(Passing through Anyang)
This is Anyang Art Park.
(They arrive at the next spot where Jong Kook has fond memories.)
- It's something else now. - This was Anyang Recreational Park.
I wonder what the sketchbooks are for.
What are we doing next?
- Okay! - Right.
This is going to be so much fun.
(They sit in front of the mysterious sketchbooks.)
I can't wait to see how fun this'll be.
- Nice. - It's going to be so much fun.
- We're ready. - Okay.
For your second stop,
you're at a scenic getaway restaurant...
- Okay! - where you can enjoy...
(A hearty meal overlooking the stream)
stream views and a hearty meal.
Who knew a place like this existed?
Check out the scenery.
(An open stream view that's ideal for a summer getaway)
This place is amazing.
- Right? - It's so pretty.
(Here, they'll fill up on nourishing, rejuvenating food.)
I can smell the baeksuk.
This used to be Anyang Recreational Park.
(They arrived at Anyang Recreational Park.)
- That's right. - So this is where it was.
You can all eat today,
though only the three winners...
won't have to pay.
- Yes, bring it. - I see.
- We have to win the game. - Lucky them.
I want to come out on top.
The game you'll play...
is Guess Who's Second.
(Mission 2: Guess Who's 2nd)
It's a simple game of guessing who.
- Guess who? - One of you...
will hear the question...
and name the person you think comes second.
- Second? - Oh, second.
- Who fits the category, right? - I get it.
The rest of you...
will debate who was chosen for second...
and make your own picks.
- Second? - Whoever guesses correctly...
(Who's the 2nd ugliest person?)
scores a point.
The quizzer also...
(Yang Se Chan)
earns a point if their pick receives...
the most votes.
I don't think Ju Yeon understood.
- Quiet. - I don't think Ju Yeon got it.
- She didn't get it. - Quiet, guys.
- I got it, okay? - She got it.
- She got it. - Yes, I got it.
- Don't talk about it. - Quiet, okay?
(Ju Yeon says she understood.)
Got it.
For the first round,
- guess who Ju Yeon put... - Me?
- Right. - in second place.
- Who Ju Yeon put in second place? - Okay.
Are you sure about this when she doesn't know the rules?
She didn't get how the game works.
(They're not sure about their first representative.)
Are you sure she should go first?
- She doesn't get it. - She didn't get it.
- Okay. - Right.
(The question is revealed first.)
- Here's the question. - Sure.
If you had met in school,
which member wouldn't you have been friends with?
Please rank the members.
- Among us, right? - That's right.
- Regardless of gender, right? - Yes.
- We're all considered the same age. - Okay, got it.
- That's right. - I have a pretty good idea.
- Second place, not first. - Yes, second.
(Ju Yeon, the representative, will pick her 2nd choice.)
- Second, not first. - This is a tough one.
- Someone you won't be friends with. - One you wouldn't be friends with.
I bet it's Ji Eun or Eun Ji.
(Guessing)
- One you wouldn't be friends with. - Based on their looks...
(Se Chan thinks it's either Ji Eun or Eun Ji.)
- Based on their looks... - Why?
- You two are too pretty. - Why?
Hold on. It could be Ye Eun.
- You two are too pretty. - I'd be besties with her.
It could be Ye Eun.
- She's so cute. - Why?
- I'd be besties with her. - I doubt Ye Eun...
(Slandering)
- was popular in school. - Actually, Ye Eun...
(Mad)
- I was extremely popular! - Hold on.
- Ye Eun... - She's...
She can be quite a lot.
(Agreeing)
I was really popular in my all-girls' middle and high school.
(While Ye Eun is trying to make them believe she was popular,)
- I mean... - In school?
(Ju Yeon picks her 2nd choice.)
Girls loved me for being cute.
- Second, right? - Regardless of gender.
That's right.
(Now, they have to guess her 2nd choice!)
- You never know. - Ju Yeon, are you done?
Yes, I'm done. I let them know.
- We have her answer. - I have a question.
(They start talking to her to figure it out.)
Ju Yeon, what kind of people...
- do you dislike? - The type.
(What type of person does Ju Yeon hate?)
Could you list three traits?
What about them can't you stand?
Think back to your school days.
- What can't you stand? - Someone who talks a lot?
Imagine you're in school with them and in the same class.
Well, someone...
- Who thinks they're pretty? - who talks too much.
- Too talkative. - Someone who talks too much.
(Ju Yeon's blacklist: The talkative one)
- Someone loud. - Someone who talks too much.
(Someone like him)
- Like Jong Kook. - That's someone you dislike?
- Jae Seok, you're out. - Someone too loud.
(Someone like him)
Jong Kook, you're out too.
I think it'll be Seok Jin.
It has to be Haha.
- It has to be Haha. - I'm not loud.
(Subjective)
I'm just naturally witty.
- No, you talk a lot. - As if.
(What are you talking about?)
- He talks a lot. - You talk way too much.
(Jae Seok is also a strong candidate.)
- That's true. - You're funny, but you talk a lot.
- Jae Seok talks a lot. - He talks a lot.
- Also, I... - What else?
- List two more traits. - Well...
Someone who's strong but...
- That's Jong Kook. - Jong Kook it is!
- "Someone who's strong but..." - That's Jong Kook.
- I'm sure of it. - That puts me in first place.
I mean strong kids...
(Ju Yeon's blacklist: The talkative one, a muscle-bound bully)
who bully people and steal things.
- I see. - "Come over here." Like that?
I didn't steal from other kids.
"Give me 50 cents." Like that?
- A bully who steals. - I'm a crusader for justice.
- A crusader for justice. - Anyway,
- here's another clue for you. - What is it?
I went to an all-girls' middle school,
high school, and university.
- Me too, except for university. - I get it.
- Okay. - It's one of the girls then.
(It's one of the girls then.)
Hold on a second.
I think there's a good chance it's Eun Ji.
- Me? - Earlier, they went...
head to head, dancing to "Catch Catch."
- I see. - Are you the type...
(The two of them had a dance battle earlier.)
to hold a grudge?
That's right. I always love being the center of attention.
- I see. - Then it's Eun Ji.
(Eun Ji stole the spotlight.)
- Eun Ji. - It's Eun Ji.
She lost to Eun Ji.
You always have to be in the spotlight, right?
(I know.)
Yes, that's right.
- Eun Ji stole her moment. - I don't like it...
(Is Eun Ji her 2nd choice?)
when others get the attention.
- Hold on. - Is it a guy or a girl?
- Okay. - Please write down your answer.
(They start writing down their answers.)
Wait. This is a tough one.
- I have no idea. - Jung Eun Ji.
- She was in a girl group too. - Eun Ji is probably in first place.
(Prediction)
- Right. - Let's do this.
(They have to guess her 2nd choice, not her 1st.)
- I think it's me. - Okay, I'm done.
- I really think it's me. - It could be anyone.
Let's do this.
Show your answers on the count of three.
(Showing their answers)
- I doubt it's me. - One, two, three.
- Haha is in second place. - Here.
- Ji Eun. - It's Ji Eun.
- I put down Ji Eun too. - Why?
(Unexpectedly, Ji Eun received 3 votes.)
- Eun Ji's in first place. - She got the same number of votes.
- Why? - I wrote Ji Hyo.
(Yu Jae Seok, Jong Kook)
- I changed my answer from Eun Ji. - Who did you write?
- It can't be me. - Jong Kook?
(Haha, Haha)
- Ji Hyo, who did you write? - Haha.
- What? - Because...
- Haha, of course. - In first place is...
(Ji Eun, Ji Eun)
Ju Yeon and I are close.
(Song Ji Hyo, Song Ji Hyo)
I think Ji Hyo's second.
I picked Ji Hyo too.
Here's why. Ju Yeon wants to shine,
(Ju Yeon wants to shine.)
- but Ji Hyo's known for her beauty. - She's so pretty.
She had side-swept bangs.
(Ji Hyo as famous for her looks back in Ilsan.)
Back then...
- Wasn't she an uljjang? - Exactly.
Ji Hyo was a stunner.
- Ji Hyo's probably in first place. - Were you an uljjang?
(Jong Kook and Ye Eun's deduction: It's not easy...)
(for pretty people to get along.)
- Yes, she was. - I see.
Ju Yeon was an uljjang too.
(Ju Yeon was also famous for her looks.)
- Here's the answer. - Hold on.
- What's the verdict? - Do you have it?
(The voting results)
- Did someone guess correctly? - Did anyone get it right?
Ji Eun got 3 votes, Haha got 2 votes,
Ji Hyo got two votes,
Jae Seok got 1 vote, and Jong Kook got 1 vote.
- So the answer... - How would I be the answer?
(Is 1 of them her 2nd choice?)
- What's the answer? - Who's in second place?
Did anyone guess correctly?
No.
- Who is it then? - We should guess again.
- Isn't it Se Chan? - Here's the correct answer.
(Who was actually number 2 on her "least likely to get close" list?)
- Sure. - Who is it?
The answer is...
- It's Eun Ji. - Who is it?
- The answer is... - I think it's Eun Ji.
- It's Ji Ye Eun. - What?
- What? - It's Ji Ye Eun.
- What? - Why?
- See? I told you. - Why?
She just goes around with someone ugly by her side.
(Ddochi, who wasn't even a candidate, was the answer!)
- No way. - She just hangs out...
- with someone less attractive. - What about the all girls' school?
(Ji Ye Eun)
I was really popular in my all-girls' middle and high school.
(In contrast to her claims)
It's not that I don't like her. It'd just be awkward.
(The reason)
- Because it'd be awkward? - I get it.
- Because it'd be awkward? - It was Ye Eun.
(The reason she wrote is revealed.)
- Let me tell you why. - What's the reason?
(Ji Ye Eun)
- The reason. - Here's why.
Her voice is too high-pitched.
- Of course. - What she actually wrote...
was "gets on my nerves."
Ju Yeon!
(Ju Yeon doesn't like high-pitched, husky voices.)
- It gets on her nerves. - She's not wrong.
- Ye Eun's like that. - Why do I get on your nerves?
- Seriously? - Ju Yeon gave us all the clues.
Someone loud...
- Someone loud. - Someone loud.
(Speaking at the same time)
I mentioned I don't really like chatty types.
- I don't talk a lot. - Right.
(Mistaken)
It was Ye Eun all along.
- Who's in 1st place? - Who's number 1?
- I bet it's Eun Ji. - Ji Hyo.
- Because she's pretty, right? - See? I told you so.
(Ji Hyo is number 1 on her "least likely to get close" list.)
- The two pretty ones... - We were on the right track.
(Asking right away)
- Why me? - They'd be rivals.
- Why me? - She'd feel threatened.
- If we were the same age... - Why her?
(Stuttering)
- and in the same class, - If you had met?
- she would've been prettier. - That's right.
(Shaking)
(It actually sounds like a compliment.)
We guessed correctly.
Ji Hyo was picked for a positive reason.
- I figured as much. - It was for something positive.
(Sad)
- That's why she's number one. - That's right.
First place is easy to guess, but second place isn't.
- It's tricky. - Second place is hard to guess.
- This is tough. - No one got it right.
- No one got it right. - Not second place.
- Second place is tricky to get. - It's tough.
(None of them couldn't earn a point on the first question!)
We should've stayed objective and remembered...
they had a moment together before the opening.
- They grew close. - Exactly.
We should've picked someone besides the other two.
(A bond has formed among the guests.)
- You're right. We talked a lot. - Let's keep going.
(It's time for the next question.)
Here's the second question.
Try to guess who Jae Seok picks for second place.
(Jae Seok is the representative this time.)
- Who I rank as second? - Yes.
The person you personally rank second in this category.
Who'd leave a partner of ten years...
if a conglomerate heir asked them out?
(Laughing)
- Second place? - Is it me?
- Yes, second place. - That's harder to guess.
- Right, 2nd place. - I can probably guess 1st place.
- No way. - I know who'll rank first.
It's either me or Seok Jin.
(These two are the prime suspects.)
Seok Jin's in first place for sure.
- Definitely. - In first place...
Seok Jin's in first place.
(Revealing)
Did you already make up your mind?
(If Seok Jin is his 1st choice, who's his 2nd?)
- Yes, Seok Jin's in 1st place. - So guess who's 2nd.
- This is hilarious. - Yes, he's in first place.
In first place?
Seok Jin will pretend to struggle with it,
but he'll dump his partner.
(A 35-year friend's cold, hard analysis)
- This is tough. - He'll pretend to feel terrible.
He'll pretend it's a hard decision.
Seok Jin will pretend to struggle with it,
(Detailed)
But after about a week,
Seok Jin will make up his mind and run to the heiress.
I'll say I have an incurable disease.
(He already has an excuse ready.)
- Then I'll leave her. - This person values money.
- Just how rich... - The money...
is this conglomerate heir?
- Totally loaded. - It's like this.
- The grandparent is the chairman. - A net worth of a trillion dollars.
(The family is worth billions of dollars.)
The family's net worth would easily be...
- It's like this. - several billion dollars.
There are a few people here who'd dump their partners...
for way less than that.
- I mean... - Grandchild or great-grandchild...
(They'd be easily swayed by much less money!)
All it takes is about three million dollars.
You don't have to go that far.
- I have a question. - Okay.
Can I bring my kids?
What?
(The father of three is thinking it through.)
Are you considering it?
Don't be like that.
- Are you considering it? - You guys.
All of you are yet unmarried.
- Okay. - We're single.
Oh, we're single.
How much were we in love for ten years?
Our ten-year love. How serious was it?
- Here's what I'm imagining. - Okay.
("I Chose a Billionaire Over Him")
Listen carefully.
Okay.
- Okay. - Is it public knowledge?
(Writer Yu starts writing.)
- It's not public. No one knew. - Okay.
You've been a celebrity,
and you were dating this person in secret for ten years.
Things right now aren't as good as they used to be.
- It's changed. - We're distant.
But it's a fact that this person was your shoulder to cry on.
They were with me when I was at my worst.
(Assistant writer)
- That's on your mind. - You're going that far?
(He adds a heartfelt detail.)
Then...
Was she there for me when I was struggling?
That's something you must keep in mind.
It's hard to leave, then.
You happened to meet them somewhere,
and this new person is pursuing you.
- The rich successor. - The rich successor.
- There's this, though. - Just one person...
- I'll tell you this much. - Okay.
The rich successor knows...
you have a boyfriend or girlfriend.
- They know that? - It's that detailed?
(These are your circumstances.)
- I'm a celebrity. - There's a lot of details.
- I'm a celebrity. - Yes.
- Am I doing well or what? - What?
Is my career stumbling?
(He also wants to know how bright his future is.)
Am I stumbling or do I have a bright future?
To be honest, you peaked, and now you're so-so.
- Oh, then... - You're so-so now.
My future is bleak.
How rich is my boyfriend of ten years?
(You want that much detail?)
- Just... - Him?
- Just... - His situation now...
- He has nothing but dreams. - His situation now...
(Assistant)
isn't going too well.
Oh, so the guy's basically...
Will we be in the news if I date this rich successor?
(He's tired now.)
Will the media report that I'm dating someone rich?
- Yes. - They would.
You're a celebrity.
- We're celebrities. - It would be in the news.
It would be in the news?
("Yang Se Chan Dating a Billionaire's Grandchild...")
You must consider that.
("Amid Rumors of Moving On Too Quickly")
That would be humiliating.
- There's a risk. - Someone...
would take the plunge despite the risk?
I've decided. Honestly...
I think this person will come first.
They come to mind straight away.
(The person who's likely to choose a billionaire over their lover)
This is so hard.
- I got this right. - It's Seok Jin or me.
(Who is his number 2 pick for a gold digger?)
We're guessing the second place?
- Yes. - Second place.
This is obvious.
(The other members also wrote down their answers.)
- It is to me. - I see it clearly.
- We must get this. - Who Jae Seok thinks...
It's difficult.
Why am I giving this so much thought?
Jae Seok, you need us to be right so you can gain points.
- Of course. - Yes.
(He only gets a point if his answer gets enough votes.)
You're writing an essay.
He's giving his reasons.
Yes, I'm writing the reason.
His reason is so lengthy.
He needs another card.
It's fine. I crossed something out.
(Jae Seok picked his 2nd choice.)
I wrote down my reasons.
I need more of you to get it right.
(Who is his 2nd choice?)
- Of course. - Yes.
(The members' answers will be revealed first.)
- Okay. - One...
Am I wrong?
Okay, one, two, three.
(Ji Hyo, Song Ji Hyo)
- I expected me. - Seok Jin's first.
I expected me.
(Haha)
- It's Seok Jin. - Wait.
Me too.
(Ji Ye Eun, Jee Seok Jin)
- It's Seok Jin. - Yang Se Chan.
(Se Chan, Yang Se Chan, Yang Se Chan)
- Let's see. - Okay.
I thought Ju Yeon, but Ye Eun?
- I had to think hard. - Everyone mentioned Se Chan.
- I had to think hard. - Yang Se Chan.
(She was thinking of choosing Se Chan, but she picked Ju Yeon.)
It's me?
(Se Chan: 3 votes, Ji Hyo: 2 votes, Haha, Seok Jin, Ye Eun: 1 vote)
At first, I thought...
(Se Chan got the most votes.)
Yes, Se Chan. I think he'll switch.
(Se Chan: 3 votes, Ji Hyo: 2 votes, Haha, Seok Jin, Ye Eun: 1 vote)
- Someone got it right. - Okay.
- Jae Seok's second place answer. - Yes.
Haha.
It's Se Chan.
(Se Chan)
(It was Se Chan, the most likely candidate!)
I wrote my name then crossed it out!
(Se Chan: 3 votes)
- Yes! - I'd written his name.
(Jae Seok will receive a point as well.)
It's obviously Se Chan.
Yang Se Chan.
(The reasons will be announced.)
- Here are the reasons. - The reasons.
"Incredible desire to be rich."
"Current stock investments are doing poorly."
- That's accurate! - Right?
That's accurate.
- The desire to... - I'd written his name.
(Se Chan's down because his stock price dropped.)
Jong Kook, Ye Eun, and Ji Hyo got it right.
(The 3 people who wrote Se Chan don't have to pay!)
You don't have to pay.
- Only you three got it? - Yes.
- Jae Seok, you're also exempt. - Okay.
(Jae Seok, who wrote the answer that got the most votes, is exempt!)
I thought really hard.
This is great.
Now you can enjoy your meal and the view together.
(It's time to eat now.)
Yay, the food is coming.
- Gosh, what is this? - The pork belly looks great.
(A mouth-watering meal is served.)
- The pork belly looks insane. - I haven't had this in a while.
(Korean comfort food)
The quality of the pork belly here is amazing.
(Golden-brown pork belly with a satisfying texture)
The pork belly. You must eat it now.
Pork belly's the best in summer. Baeksuk with sarcodon mushrooms?
Baeksuk with sarcodon mushrooms.
(Rejuvenating, rich baeksuk with sarcodon mushrooms)
It's an awesome stream-side meal.
It looks delicious.
The drumstick. You must eat by hand.
- Look. - Is it safe to eat now?
(He tries the drumstick first.)
Seok Sam, you must eat now.
- Now? - Yes.
It's good.
The drumstick? Find the other one?
(Eun Ji dips it in the broth.)
The glutinous rice is nice.
It's good.
Isn't it great?
(Exclaiming)
- I found it. - It's tasty.
(The vacationers are hooked on the baeksuk.)
- Is it good? - Yes, it's good.
(Spilling)
You're spilling it all.
You've never done this?
(No)
What's going on, Ju Yeon?
(Ju Yeon is clumsy somehow.)
- I'll give you some baeksuk. - Okay.
(He knows exactly what he likes.)
The breast. I don't like thigh meat.
You want a leg? I'll give you one.
(Miscommunication)
- The styles clash. - Ju Yeon's spilling it everywhere.
(She misheard it and put a drumstick in the bowl.)
Ju Yeon, I get how you feel,
- but stop it. - It's overflowing!
Okay.
(Passing it to Jae Seok)
- It's my appreciation. - Okay, thanks.
I said I don't like drumsticks and she gave me one.
You don't like drumsticks?
(He doesn't trust her.)
I'll serve myself.
- You didn't ask for a drumstick? - No.
Why do I have nothing but chicken skin?
- Ju Yeon, I appreciate it, but... - Ju Yeon!
(Sagging)
What is this, Ju Yeon?
(Everyone's displeased with their servings.)
I haven't done this much.
(She puts the leaner part this time.)
The dry breast meat. Here you go.
- Thanks, Ju Yeon. - I'm not sure if that's right.
(Smiling)
(After serving her elders, Ju Yeon eats too.)
- This is... - It's tasty.
Oh, it's delicious. The broth is rich.
It's done.
(While they're eating baeksuk, the pork belly is perfectly cooked.)
- I want some pork belly. - Pork belly?
(She eats a sizzling piece.)
It's tasty.
(Savoring)
(Giggling)
It's delicious.
(The best vacation is to eat well in an air-conditioned room.)
- The broth is rich. - What's the title?
Gosh, it's tasty.
The pork belly is amazing.
I'm in last place.
You're in last place?
(She's the last one to pay.)
I have to pay last this time.
The lunch cost a total of 350 dollars.
(They paid before the meal earlier.)
That's a lot.
- Six of you, excluding the four... - The rest must pay.
have to pay.
It's 350 dollars?
(Eun Ji paid first.)
Then...
I'll pay 6.5 dollars.
(Cave: 5 dollars, Restaurant: 6.5 dollars)
(Similar amount as before)
They might think I paid too little.
(Ju Yeon's payments)
Ten dollars.
(A generous amount)
They'll select a member, not a guest.
(Ji Eun will select a member, not a guest.)
The chance I get picked is over 50 percent.
(Worried)
I must pay this much to avoid getting named.
(How much did Haha spend?)
- Thirty dollars? - Thirty dollars.
- Twenty? - Thirty.
(Seok Sam promised to pay 30 dollars.)
- Between 20 and 30? - No, 30.
Can you pay 60 dollars?
Of course. How much is that? Six times six is 36?
(Se Chan promised to pay 60 dollars.)
Yes. I'm serious.
(Did they keep their promises?)
We agreed to pay 30 dollars each.
(Ji Eun is the last one to pay.)
So Seok Jin said...
(Eun Ji: 6.5 dollars, Ju Yeon: 10 dollars)
he would pay 30 dollars.
Se Chan said he'd pay 60.
Wouldn't they have paid at least 50 between them?
(In total)
All I did so far was grill meat.
I only ate one piece so far. I haven't finished my meal.
(How much is left to pay out of the 350-dollar food bill?)
The amount remaining after the others paid...
is 322 dollars.
It's 322 dollars.
They're really mean.
(Slam!)
(The 5 only paid 28 dollars.)
I must be paying the price for paying little earlier.
If you pick out the person who paid the least,
(She needs to find the person who paid the least amount.)
that person will cover this for you.
(That person will pay 322 dollars then.)
The reason I can't tell...
is because out of those who paid,
there's Seok Jin, Se Chan, and Haha.
(They play the game so well!)
(Dumbfounded)
How can I tell?
(Ji Eun came back furious.)
You people are so horrible.
- Why? - What's wrong?
Why?
Why are you upset?
(Shameless)
- Everyone paid 60. - You guys.
- Se Chan and Haha. - You aren't ashamed at all?
What was the remainder?
She came back a total thug.
None of you have the right to act nonchalant.
- Why? - Why?
(A voice crack)
How much was it? Does it make sense?
- It's not right, Ji Eun. - How much did you pay?
- I barely ate too. - Why are you so angry?
Six of you had to cover a total of 350 dollars.
- Yes. How much was left? - The amount Ji Eun had to pay...
was 322 dollars.
- What? - That's not fair.
(Eun Ji: 6.5 dollars, Ju Yeon: 10 dollars)
From how much to how much?
- That's 322 out of 350 dollars. - That's mean.
(The 3 of them paid 11.5 dollars in total.)
The rest of you paid a few dollars each.
We paid 12 dollars.
I'll tell you the smallest amount someone here paid.
It's 2.5 dollars.
- How much? - How could you?
After Ji Hyo was caught for paying a cent and raised the minimum.
That person must get hot water poured on them.
(You should pour hot water over the culprit.)
- That's too much. - Pour hot broth on their hands.
Who paid 2 dollars 50? Where's your conscience?
(1 of Seok Jin, Se Chan, and Haha paid 2.5 dollars.)
That person paid 2 dollars 50 to avoid getting caught.
- I think so. - They were being clever.
Ji Eun, if you successfully point out...
(Will Ji Eun be able to catch the culprit?)
the person who paid 2 dollars 50 cents,
they must pay 322 dollars on top of that.
Ji Eun, I'll come clean. I...
You don't have to believe me, but I'm telling the truth.
I don't believe you.
- Se Chan... - Ji Eun, hear me out.
(In a rush)
I thought you'd name me,
- so on purpose... - Yes, I think you would.
I paid extra.
Despite everything.
(Haha paid...)
(3 dollars!)
Three dollars.
I think I should pay this much.
(It wasn't Haha who paid the least!)
If you pick me? It wasn't me, and you'll lose out.
(It's either Seok Sam or Se Chan who paid 2.5 dollars!)
- Who could it be? - It's not me.
- Personally, Ji Eun. - I'm curious.
- It's not Haha. - It's really not me.
Seok Jin's voice is a bit too high.
- Okay. - I think it's him.
I do too. He keeps...
(She starts pressuring him.)
Look into my eyes. Know that I'm sincere.
He is stingy. Hey.
- So here is what I think. - I...
- The one who paid 2.50 dollars... - It's Haha.
thought he wouldn't be last.
The one who paid 2.50 dollars...
- must be very surprised right now. - That's right.
- Who could it be? - I paid more...
because I expected this to happen.
(Detective Ji Eun is contemplating.)
Listen. Who would be so petty to add just 50 cents?
Who would be so petty?
Seeing as how the amount is 2.50 dollars,
it's Seok Jin.
- I paid a lot. - Think about who added 50 cents...
(Was it the petty Seok Sam who threw in 50 cents?)
to two dollars.
Listen.
- I... - Who would be so petty...
to add just 50 cents?
- I... I'll pick one. - Who would be so petty?
Even though the two of them are busy explaining themselves...
he is absorbed in eating.
Me?
I paid a lot.
- Please. - You're right. It's Seok Jin.
(He eats again.)
That's the correct answer.
Ji Eun, there is a serious twist.
(Is he the culprit? Or does he just have a big appetite?)
Do you think it's me?
You're eating with so much gusto.
For goodness' sake. Then why would I be so relaxed?
It isn't me.
Fine. Go ahead and pick me.
But think about your future.
I'll pick Jee Seok Jin.
For goodness' sake.
(Ji Eun chooses Seok Sam in the end.)
- You picked Seok Jin. - I bet it's Se Chan.
(Is it Seok Sam who played dirty?)
- She is right. - She is right indeed.
She chose correctly. It's Seok Jin.
- She is right. - Seok Jin added 50 cents.
You're correct.
She is right.
- Seok Jin, are you serious? - Ji Eun.
(She caught the person who paid the least amount!)
- Ji Eun. - Seok Jin added 50 cents.
- I could figure it out... - But...
through deductions.
It was the choice of someone who had played many games.
They wouldn't add 50 cents.
Did you guys pay more than 2.50 dollars?
- Yes. - The two of them too?
Seok Jin, I paid a lot.
(They paid 6 dollars and 3 dollars respectively.)
- Me too. I bet I paid the most. - I paid a lot.
I'm in trouble.
- Seok Jin, you need to pay... - How did you know?
- a total of 324.50 dollars. - You weren't saying anything.
- Ji Eun, you don't need to pay. - How did she get him?
- My goodness. - How did you know?
- You know, - Seriously, how did you know?
When you revealed the amount,
- I could get a sense of things. - I could make deductions.
- I could make deductions. - Those who are used to games...
(If someone paid 50 cents, it's most likely Seok Sam!)
would pay 1 cent or 2.50 dollars. Isn't that right?
- That's right. - With that amount,
(Ji Eun caught Seok Sam with her sharp instincts.)
I thought I'd place second.
- Yes. Two dollars and fifty cents. - That's right.
Now, I can eat in peace.
We rack our brains so much.
- It's tasty. - Gosh, it's good.
(She can finally taste the food.)
Ji Eun, please eat up.
Protein.
You'll divide into two teams for the next location.
- Really? - Yes.
You'll go to a cool place that'll give you chills.
(Vacation course 3)
- Sounds good. - Okay.
What will we do next?
It's so hot.
(The next vacation spot to beat the heat)
This is the place.
This place sits in the middle of a popular neighborhood.
I think it'll be scary.
(Even the entrance gives them chills.)
- I can't do this. - Seriously.
(Horror-themed escape room)
This is too much.
(Horror escape room)
Is it an escape room?
It's a haunted house ride.
- Is it a scary place? - It's scary.
I don't get scared easily.
- Really? - Yes.
- Why? - I get scared very easily.
(Team Jae Seok arrives at the horror escape room.)
- Gosh. - Why did you bring us here?
- It's for a scary experience. - It's a haunted house ride.
- Look over there. - Gosh, you startled me!
Hey, you startled me!
- Haha! - Hey.
(A ghost frame)
- Look over there. - Gosh, you startled me!
(Haha gets startled as well.)
Hey, you startled me!
- Haha! - Hey.
Why did you only notice it now?
You said you don't get scared easily.
That startled me.
(She says one thing and does another.)
- Oh, my. - This is...
She said she doesn't get scared easily.
- When you have a scary experience, - I'm scared for real.
you get chills...
(A scary experience can actually lower your body temperature.)
and your body temperature drops.
I'm not so desperate to lower my body temperature.
- I don't want to pay for this. - Seriously.
- I really don't want to. - This is a place...
where you can experience realistic horrors.
(They can experience bone-chilling horrors here.)
- All right. - For goodness' sake.
It's your goal to escape...
from a hospital where the hospital director wanders...
in search of test subjects.
I can't do this.
(He is fed up already.)
Only one person who enjoys the scary escape room...
will receive an exemption card.
Maybe they'll pick someone who screams the most...
- or the least. - I know.
- As for the order... - That's right.
- Are we going alone? - Jae Seok...
- Let us go together. - Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Ju Yeon.
- What? - The three of you are a team.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Ju Yeon.
- I want to be in a group of three. - Haha and Ji Eun.
- I want to be in a group of three. - In this group...
(Haha and Ji Eun are on the same team.)
Ji Eun, if a ghost appears,
I'll push you toward it.
You really shouldn't do that.
I get scared easily too.
I apologize in advance. I don't know what I'll do.
(Ji Eun teams up with Haha, the scaredy-cat.)
- I really don't know. - Apparently,
these things don't scare Ju Yeon.
- Who? - I don't get scared easily.
(Ju Yeon says she is fearless.)
- But a picture frame scared you. - Really?
That picture frame...
(Doubting)
- Would you guide us? - Just you wait.
- Would you take the lead? - I'll do that.
(Brave)
- Go ahead. - Okay.
Then both of you...
(Without hesitation)
- I can't do it. - You can't do it.
The 2 of you will wait. The 3 of you will go 1st.
- Let us go 1st. - Are we going 1st?
- We're going 1st. - I'd rather go 1st.
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Ju Yeon will go first.)
- Let's get done with it. - In any case...
- Seriously. - There are actors inside.
- Are there actors inside? - Please line up here.
- There are actors inside. - Seriously,
(Ju Yeon looks calm.)
this is driving me crazy.
- There are actors inside. - In there...
- Am I going first? - Ju Yeon is the leader.
(Take the lead.)
Yes.
This is the horror switch.
(The adventure begins at the flip of a switch.)
Who wants to push it up?
(Employee: "Who wants to push it up?")
Ju Yeon. Ju Yeon will do everything.
Push it all the way up.
Okay. That's good.
(Leader Ju Yeon pushes it up for the scaredy-cats.)
- Now, the hospital door will open. - Gosh, this is...
You'll find the same-looking switches inside.
(They have to flip the switch in each room to move on.)
- Eden Hospital? - Push them down as you go forward.
- The door is open. - Keep that in mind.
- Seok Jin, stop it. - The three of you will enter now.
Go all the way down.
Gosh, this is... We need to go down further.
(Stairs leading into pitch-black darkness)
We need to go down further. It's the basement.
Hey.
Go all the way down.
Gosh, this is... We need to go down further.
(Ju Yeon takes the lead without hesitation.)
- Come on down. - Has it started?
- Yes, it has. - Hey.
- Hey. - Come on down.
- It's cool. - Be careful.
It's cold.
- Go all the way down the stairs. - This place is too scary.
(Chilly)
- I'm so scared. - It's scary.
Please.
- It isn't scary. - Gosh!
(Everyone froze when the screen suddenly lit up.)
- For goodness' sake. - I'm so scared.
It's very similar to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
- The vibes are very similar. - It's very similar.
What's this video?
It's so scary.
(A doctor experiments on people to save his sick son.)
This is driving me crazy.
- This is... - I don't know about this.
(They must escape before they become his test subjects.)
Please.
What's that?
It's well-made.
(Thundering)
For goodness' sake.
(The thunder makes their hearts race.)
The special effects are no joke.
This is driving me crazy.
- I can't believe it. - I don't think...
(Appearing)
What's that? Hold on!
Quiet down!
- I can't believe it. - I don't think...
What's that? Hold on!
Quiet down!
(A dizzying welcome from the very start)
I think there is something.
We can go forward when the door opens automatically.
(Wind comes out!)
It's the wind.
- What? - It's the wind.
What?
It's the wind.
(The men's screams startle Ju Yeon even more.)
(Creaking)
(The door opens.)
- We need to go in. - Are you confident?
- Yes. Just follow me. - Ju Yeon.
(Ju Yeon takes the lead.)
Let's go back.
- Let's go back. - I'm seriously scared.
This is driving me crazy.
(The two chickens become timid.)
- Come on. - The back...
(Their over-the-top reactions will scare her more.)
- I mean... - Hey.
(The billing office looks creepy.)
- What? - I think there is someone.
I think there is someone.
- Where? - Who?
Other rooms...
(Whirring)
(The screens suddenly turn on.)
It's so...
Welcome to the Eden Hospital.
It's okay if you don't have a family.
We'll become your family...
and take care of you until the end.
- You don't need to be my family. - You'll be comfortable here.
Eden Hospital will continue to...
- Ju Yeon, are you okay? - Will continue to...
I'm okay.
(Snap)
- What? - What is it?
(He bumps into the air conditioner.)
(Screaming)
- What's up with you? - I get more startled...
- because of you guys! - They did something.
What did they do? I didn't notice anything.
(They did nothing.)
- It's an air conditioner. - It hurts.
- What should we do? - What should we do?
(A budget-friendly guest who gets scared without any special effects)
- Which way do we need to go? - Gosh.
Wait. Don't we need to push up that switch?
(The switch)
Didn't she tell us to push it down?
- We should push it down. - Oh, I forgot.
(They need to push down the switch to go to the next location.)
(Ju Yeon pushes down the switch bravely.)
(Whispering)
- For goodness' sake. - What's this?
Don't do this.
(As she flips the switch, an eerie whisper echoes through the room.)
This is...
Stop it already.
(Did you call for me?)
- Hold on. - What?
- There is someone. - Hey.
- Who? - Over there.
(Blurry)
- Who? - Can you see her?
- Where? - Over there.
- Over there. For goodness' sake. - Seriously.
(Shutting his eyes)
For goodness' sake.
(The billing office ghost came to work late.)
(The door opens behind the ghost!)
- We can't go this way, right? - Wait.
- We need to go past her. - She is moving.
(They have to pass by the ghost to move on to the next location!)
- She is moving. - There is a ghost.
There she is.
What? Who is she?
(Who's that person?)
Please. Can't you see her?
How am I supposed to know who she is?
I haven't seen her before.
(No one knows who the ghost is.)
Who is she?
- This is driving me crazy. - This is driving me crazy.
- She is just standing there. - I guess we need to go past her.
She is an NPC.
- An NPC. - Gosh.
Go.
We need to keep going.
- That ghost... - We have to go past her.
- Gosh. - Please.
- Please don't move. - Don't talk to the ghosts.
Please don't move.
- I don't know about this. - Ju Yeon, go.
You keep telling Ju Yeon to go.
Please.
(He lets his junior lead the way and follows closely behind.)
There is nowhere to run.
Wait.
- Really? Is it okay? - Come this way.
Hold on. Why is it so dark?
- Gosh. - Please.
- Please don't move. - Gosh.
Please don't move.
- Quiet down. - Stay there!
(Don't go!)
(Screaming)
What?
(Please save us.)
Don't follow us!
- Gosh. - Don't follow us!
(While the first team members are scared out of their minds,)
Don't follow us!
- For goodness' sake! - Seriously.
(they are waiting outside, listening to all the screams.)
What should we do?
Even Ju Yeon is screaming.
(Having mixed feelings)
She is screaming the loudest.
What's this?
What is it?
What will I do if this appears in my dream tonight?
Go over there.
I live alone.
(Sniffing)
- All right. - It's that way.
(He already feels sick.)
Seriously.
So listen.
Since they went as a group of three, let us go with a cameraman.
That's a good idea. Seriously.
But it's a bit cramped inside.
- They went as a group of 3. - There are 3 of them now.
Let us go with Hyo Im.
(Head writer)
- Then... - Let us go with Chan Hee.
Chan Hee?
(The cowardly siblings are desperate for an extra member.)
Three of them went in together.
- That's right. Please help us out. - Give us one more person.
Since we're in my neighborhood, I'll call over my friend, Geun Sik.
(Mapo-gu)
(Geun Sik, Haha's friend, looks like he could fight a ghost)
Geun Sik won't work since he gets scared more easily.
I read in the description that you could give up.
- Yes. - Many people give up...
(Thinking alike)
- without finishing. - I asked the staff.
Many people do that.
Thirty percent of the customers do that.
(While the cowardly siblings are thinking about quitting)
- It's near here. - Who keeps touching me?
(The 3 have barely escaped the ghost.)
What?
This door opens. Gosh, that startled me.
How did they make...
such an elaborate setup here?
Gosh.
(The door at the end of the stairs)
This is...
- My neck hurts. - What?
(When she opens it...)
- Is it an automatic door? - What?
- What is it? - What is it?
How will we go past them?
(What's inside?)
This door is locked.
(Beyond the door...)
- What is it? - What is it?
(are many mannequins.)
How will we go past them?
- Oh, no. - Seriously.
Seriously, this is...
This is driving me crazy.
My body aches already.
(He has a cramp in his shoulders.)
- Hold on. Please let us through. - My neck hurts.
(Still, Ju Yeon leads the way.)
- Please. - My goodness.
- Ju Yeon. - Hold on.
Didn't you say that you wouldn't get scared?
The camera...
- Hold on. - Hold on.
- Oh, s... - The camera...
You can't swear.
Where are you going?
(Don't go!)
(Peek-a-boo)
(Scared out of their minds)
Oh, my!
(Flocking together)
Oh, my! What was that?
- Oh, my! What was that? - Please.
(Not-so-nice words)
- What? - Why are you doing this?
(Blurted it out of reflex)
Why... Why are you doing this?
Gosh, that startled me. From the back...
(Crawling)
(She crawls on her fours to get away quickly.)
From the back, the ghost suddenly appeared.
- My neck hurts. - My goodness.
Oh, my knees.
- What? - I...
I bumped into the stairs.
(He bumped into the stairs while he was running away.)
Oh, my!
- Is my camera okay? - Let me see it.
- Hold on. My camera... - It's fine.
(The professional entertainer worries about the angle.)
- I... - From the back,
(They move to the next spot while clenching at their hearts.)
- Did someone come? - the ghost grabbed my shoulders.
Oh, my. Really?
Wait. We need to stand here.
- We need to stand here. - Here.
- All 3 of us need to stand here. - All 3 of us need to do it.
(They need to stand on the eye mark to go to the next location.)
Do we need to get an X-ray scan?
(They stand on the mark.)
- What are we supposed to do? - It's an X-ray scan.
No.
The camera...
What's going on?
- My goodness. - What?
(Rattling)
My goodness.
What?
- It's this way. - Run!
(Hurrah!)
- Run! - What?
- It's this way. - Run!
- Run! - Run away!
(Jae Seok runs away first.)
- Run away! - Which way?
(Screaming)
Stop it!
- Run! - Run away!
(A ghost was hiding behind the curtains!)
(Hopping)
(He comes face-to-face with it.)
Stop it!
(Crying)
- Stop it! Please. - Mommy!
(She bursts into tears in the end.)
Please.
- Which way? - Come here.
(Ju Yeon pushes their backs.)
Come this way.
- What's this? - Oh, no!
What's this?
(Sliding out)
(Give me my leg.)
Someone grabbed my leg!
- Oh, no. - Someone grabbed my leg!
Don't grab my leg!
- Please. - Someone grabbed my leg!
Please don't grab my leg.
Hurry up.
(Ju Yeon acted tough, but she freaked out.)
Didn't you say that you wouldn't get scared?
- I mean... - Haha will die.
(Even the ghost hesitates at the fuss they're making.)
My goodness.
What should we do?
(Haha and Ji Eun are about to start.)
Both of you are Korean, right?
Yes.
- Are you ready? - I quit.
You can't quit since you haven't entered yet.
(Employee)
- Both of you are Korean, right? - Yes.
Once you push up the switch,
you'll be transferred to another dimension.
(Employee)
Who wants to push up the switch?
- Haha. - She will do it. Ji Eun.
(Recommending each other)
(In the end, Ji Eun pushes up the switch.)
Push it up all the way. That's good.
Now, go all the way down the stairs.
(They really enter now.)
What am I going to do?
(Stamping)
- What am I going to do? - Hey.
You'll get more scared if you keep saying so.
(Acting tough)
- Let's go. - You can do it.
- Hey. Hey, come on out. - Hey, don't do that.
(She shouts loudly to feel less scared.)
- Don't do that. - Why not?
(He's done acting tough.)
It's scaring me.
- Okay. - Wait.
(The cowardly senior takes the lead.)
- Let's go together. - Okay. Let's go.
- It's so scary. - I quit.
I quit.
(He quits before going halfway down the stairs.)
- Go all the way down the stairs. - I quit.
(Go all the way down the stairs.)
What should I do? Wait for me.
Let's do this. It isn't scary.
(It takes them forever to climb down the stairs.)
I'm seriously scared.
It isn't scary. People pay for this.
Okay. Let's hurry up and go.
I won't go.
(Startled by the automatic door)
- Hey. The door opened. - Don't do this.
Haha, wait. Wait for me.
- Wait for me. - Hurry over here.
(Ji Eun is as cowardly as Haha.)
Hey, you get scared more easily than me.
If you cover your ears,
(A tip)
- you won't get startled so much. - You're right.
(Tip number 1 for the cowards: Covering the ears)
Keep your eyes on the floor.
(Tip number 2 for the cowards:)
(Keep the eyes on the floor and walk sideways.)
(The video plays.)
What is it?
- Okay. Don't be scared. - Okay.
Immerse yourself in this. You're a detective.
(Tip number 3 for the cowards: Imagining filming a crime drama)
- You've played cool characters. - Okay.
I'm filming a drama right now.
Will continue to...
- What? Continue on forward? - What are we supposed to do?
Continue on forward?
We don't know what to do.
- Hey. - We need to push it down.
(He finds a switch.)
- Push it down. - Push it down.
(Pushing the job onto her)
(When they push down the switch)
- Be careful. - There is something.
- Hey! Someone came out! - What is it?
- Hey! Someone came out! - Where?
(They move back like crabs.)
Where are you going?
- It's a ghost! - I see her.
- Am I wrong? - You're right. It's a ghost.
(She is more daring than expected.)
What?
Let's go together.
Hold on. I farted.
It's okay. It doesn't smell.
Let's go together.
I'm sorry.
- I get scared so easily. - Please...
Please make it less scary.
I'm sorry. I'm about to poop my pants.
- We can't go forward. - Seriously.
She is a bigger coward than I am.
- Seriously. - I'll let out diarrhea. Seriously.
(Dirty)
- I warned you. - Don't grab us.
(Threatening to let it out)
Then you'll need to clean up the mess.
(Giggling)
- Did you laugh? - No.
(The ghost laughs at the absurd threat.)
So don't touch us.
- Can't you go first? - I can't.
(Firm)
(In the end, Haha goes first.)
Hurry up, Ji Eun.
(Creaking)
- Don't do it. - What's this?
(Rustling)
Don't do it.
(Serious)
For goodness' sake. What is it?
(Screaming)
- What? - I told you not to do it!
(Scolding)
What is it? What?
I told you not to do it!
(Pointing fingers at a ghost)
- Hey. - Move out of the way!
What? I told you not to touch us.
(The ghost gets scolded for doing her job.)
Which way do we need to go? We don't know.
(Sorry.)
I'm sorry. Don't touch us.
I'm so scared.
(After scolding the ghost, they arrive at...)
- Ji Eun, we're doing well. - How far...
How far have we come? We want to get out now.
(the mannequin room with a hidden ghost.)
Hold on.
- What? - There is something.
I think this is the real deal.
I think there will be a ghost among them.
(Sharp)
(After getting fooled a few times, Ji Eun got the hang of it.)
Not all of them are mannequins.
- You seem to be doing fine, so... - No.
- Take the lead just this once. - No.
All right.
- Hey. - Hey.
Haha, come with me.
(Let me come with you guys!)
(Screaming)
(Dropping to the floor)
Are you okay?
(Calm)
I told you that there would be someone.
Hurry up. We need to run away.
(Deflating)
Haha, are you okay?
Meanie!
(I'm not okay.)
He is crying.
It's that person.
(Ji Eun got immune to the ghosts after scolding them a few times.)
- Are you okay now? - I think so. Hurry up.
Go first.
I'll follow you.
(While Ji Eun becomes brave and takes the lead)
(The leading team finds a switch)
Hold on.
- You startled me. - Push it up.
Push it down.
(Reaching)
(Crying)
This is driving me crazy.
- You do it. - This is driving me crazy.
(The nonstop horror is driving him mad.)
You do it, Jae Seok.
It touched my hand.
- Seriously. - It touched my hand.
- It's down. - Okay. Let's go.
(When they push down the switch,)
(baby's cry fills the room.)
- What? - What's this?
Right now...
- Please. - This is driving me crazy.
- Which way is it? - Let's hurry up.
(The door opens slowly.)
- Let's hurry up. - I want to get out now.
Let's stop already.
- Please. - Seriously. Please.
(They put the cry behind them and reach someplace.)
Hey.
- Let's hurry up. - It'll open.
(A morgue, where corpses are kept)
- It's this way. - Which way?
- This way. - This way.
- Let's go. - We need to stand there.
- It's a morgue. - Here.
- Hurry up. It's the eye mark. - It's a morgue.
(The mark)
- The eye mark. - Let's hurry up.
(Covered in sweat)
I think someone will jump out.
(Correct)
- Please. - Stay away!
(Crying again)
Stay away!
- Please. - Seriously.
(The morgue refrigerators suddenly open and close.)
- Come on. - Don't come out.
- We didn't do anything wrong. - Seriously.
Stop it already.
(Wind)
(Screaming)
What is it?
Please.
(At that moment,)
I think someone will come.
(someone exits a morgue refrigerator.)
When will this end?
- I mean... Someone is here. - Someone is here.
- Someone is here. - Someone is here.
- Someone is here. - Wait.
- Someone is here. I saw him. - Someone is here.
(A strange man with a grotesque face)
- Mommy! - I saw him!
It's the "Scream" mask.
I'm sorry.
Ju Yeon, you...
(Sliding down)
Mommy!
(Ju Yeon's legs give out.)
Please.
(The strange man suddenly begins to go wild.)
- What's up with him? - Stop it.
What's wrong with him?
(Striding)
Why are you doing this?
- Why are you doing this? - Open the door!
- Open the door! - It won't open.
Mom.
(Hello...)
How old will I be when I'm not scared anymore?
(He's 60 this year.)
- Goodness. - Mom.
(Crying)
Don't.
- Don't come. - Ju Yeon.
- You said you weren't scared. - You said you were fine.
- You're on the floor. - You said you weren't scared.
(Ju Yeon cries for her mom when she said she wasn't scared.)
You...
You said you'd lead the way.
- He's still here. - Don't do it.
- Excuse me? - Sir.
(After causing a mess, the guy starts eating.)
Please let us go.
Where should we... Do we have to go out?
- Let's get past him. - Let's get past him. Don't come.
(Walking sneakily)
(They walk past him quietly not to upset him.)
Be careful.
(Where do you think you're going?)
- It's this way. - This way.
(They see the exit sign on the hallway.)
This way.
- Run! - Run!
Go!
- He's coming! - Run!
(Wait for me!)
Run! Go up!
- Go up! - Come!
(Where do you think you're going?)
Open the door!
- Come up! - Come up!
Come up! Hurry, Ju Yeon.
(Ju Yeon is about to pass out.)
Ju Yeon! Come here, Ju Yeon!
Come quickly!
This way.
(They must get out as soon as possible!)
Go.
Run.
Go, go!
Run!
(They finally see some bright light!)
(Sprinting)
Run!
- What is this? - Goodness.
(Completely beat)
It was too much!
- Hey. - This is so annoying.
- Ju Yeon. - Really.
- You said you weren't scared. - You said you weren't scared.
I miss my mom. I'm not easily scared.
(Ju Yeon became such a good daughter.)
I miss my mom.
- Goodness. - It was too much.
It was too much. I think I scraped my skin.
- It's scraped. - It's scraped.
(Seok Sam is injured.)
- Are you all right? - Right here.
- At the stairs. - At the stairs.
(He was attacked by the mannequin ghost.)
It was really scary.
(Just as the three early team members catch their breath,)
Ju Yeon.
(Haha is in tears.)
I told you there was something there.
(Patting his back)
It's okay. Get up.
(Feeling miserable)
Get up. Stop drooling!
Are you drooling? I was startled.
(Meanwhile, Ji Eun is starting to relax.)
You turn it off.
(The switch)
You should step aside then.
(He's in the way.)
(What a pain in the neck.)
Goodness.
Why can't I give up?
I was told I could give up if I couldn't take it.
(Haha is still talking about giving up halfway.)
I'm going to run!
(He almost died a few more times after that!)
- Goodness! - I'm going to run.
Where are you?
My heart hurts so much.
I'm learning martial arts these days.
(To the ghost)
- I'm the Mapo-gu Sheriff. - I learn martial arts.
(She volunteers as the coward's bodyguard.)
- Stop right there. - Stop.
(Hi-yah)
Where are you going? We should go together.
(Loyal Ji Eun stays by his side.)
- Come quickly! - We should go together.
(Push!)
(She was bounced off after hitting Haha.)
We should go together.
Goodness.
Hey!
(The farting machine runs away by himself to survive.)
Run!
Why are you going alone?
(Racing with his sphincter that gave out)
(Screaming)
(He fortunately made it out before he had an accident.)
He's the worst out of all of us.
She's worse than me.
What are you talking about? I protected you.
Ji Eun is loyal, though.
I told him...
- that we should go together. - I farted like nine times.
But she stayed by my side until the end.
She's brave.
(Loyal Ji Eun overcame the smell.)
She said...
she learned taekwondo because she was cornered.
When she was cornered,
(The taekwondo girl beat the ghosts.)
she said, "I learned taekwondo!" It was like a movie.
(Take this!)
Did you have a cool and good time?
- Cool? - I'm sweating.
It wasn't cool.
- Are you joking with us? - It's so hot.
Who tries to make it cool like this?
My head hurts.
The payment is the combined amount...
(They will pay at once, adding Team Jong Kook's costs too.)
- for both teams. - Yes.
- Let's move... - We paid for this?
(He can't believe it.)
- We have to pay? - Seriously.
- Let's go. - You have to pay.
It was so scary.
(They head to the final payment.)
It's so hot.
(They got rid of the heat completely at the creepy vacation spot.)
- Hey. - Are you all right, Seok Jin?
- Welcome back. - You guys...
- Come on. - What is it?
(Team Jong Kook was waiting for the drained members.)
We almost froze to death.
- We almost... - What are you talking about?
(Which icy-cold vacation spot did Team Jong Kook go to?)
- We almost froze to death. - We almost froze to death.
- What are you talking about? - This...
is Korea's first ice cafe, were you can experience...
(A -5°C ice cafe!)
- the refrshing chill of -5°C. - It's cold.
- It's cold. - It's cold.
(Flustered)
(In the ice kingdom, you even make your own drinks.)
(Breaking)
(They escaped the heat to face a brutal summer vacation.)
- Eun Ji. - How is it? Is it okay?
(She's forced to drink iced Americano.)
Is it okay?
- Where do I put this? - They're wearing coats.
(The cold snap weakens even the muscles.)
- They wore coats. - Where do I put this?
- If you get inside like this... - Take your arm out.
(They lose their minds and go after other people's fur.)
- You'll get hurt. - Are you a zombie?
(There's a Cerberus.)
- I need one too. - I was already wearing one.
Look up at the sky
Snow is falling white
(Fierce teamwork builds in the freezing cold.)
You should enjoy!
(They enjoyed the summer vacation that froze them to their bones.)
It's cold! It's cold!
- That's really... - That would have been nice.
(So envious)
Before the last payment,
I'll announce the members from each team...
(1 person from each team who had the best vacation...)
who'll be exempted.
(will be exempt from the payment.)
- First, from the ice cafe, - Yes.
(Team Jong Kook's exempt member)
Eun Ji, who wore the fewest fur clothes, will be exempted.
(Eun Ji enjoyed the freezing cold without any cold-weather gear.)
Hey.
(The weak and furry members must pay.)
- Come on. - It was so cold.
- It was cold. - I wouldn't have worn it...
if you had told me.
- From the haunted experience... - I suffered an injury.
(Team Jae Seok's exempt member who went to the haunted house)
(Appealing to them)
- I think I... - Me.
(Raising her hand)
The person who got startled the most.
I got him through it while comforting him.
I only cried once.
She said she wasn't afraid of such things,
but she practically cried. Ju Yeon will be exempted.
(Ju Yeon, who cried despite acting tough, is exempted.)
Ju Yeon...
Ju Yeon shows off so much.
(Embarrassed)
The employees were the most satisfied with Ju Yeon.
(Writer)
- Really? - Really?
(The best customer for making the ghost feel proud)
They felt fulfilled by their work.
- Run! - Run!
Run!
(Feeling happy)
Come up!
- Come up! - Run!
(Her reaction made their job worthwhile.)
That's right.
(Thanks for the exemption.)
After enjoying the last experience,
Team Jae Seok spent 110 dollars,
(Haunted house: 110 dollars)
and Team Jong Kook spent 197 dollars.
(Ice cafe: 197 dollars)
We spent that much money?
The total amount is 307 dollars.
Why did you use so much money?
- Goodness. - It was expensive.
(As much as they enjoyed, the price is expensive.)
- Then let's pick one each. - Okay.
(They will draw lots to decide the payment order.)
- It was a lot. - Here.
(8 people will need to pay.)
Please!
I hope...
(The person to pay last will definitely need to pay most of it!)
- I won't be the 8th person. - You can check.
- My debt is around 300 dollars. - I...
(Seok Sam has paid the most so far.)
- Eight! - My favorite number...
It's one.
(Luckily, he draws 1.)
That's good.
- I'm number two. - What a relief.
(Lucky)
- I'm number seven. - One.
(He avoids the last number.)
I'm the eighth person.
(Oh, no.)
- I'm number seven. - Yes!
(Payment order: Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Haha, Ji Eun, Ji Hyo,)
(Ye Eun, Se Chan, Jae Seok)
I'm number two.
- Okay! - Why am I eighth again?
I'll go first.
(He needs to catch the person to remain in the top rank.)
I have to catch the person again.
I was caught earlier. They all wrote a larger amount than I thought.
(Number 1 Seok Jin goes first.)
I wouldn't be the last one if I write this amount, right?
(Sighs)
I spent 324.5 dollars.
I can totally feel it. I wouldn't be last.
(Seok Sam had to pay for everything...)
(because he was caught trying to avoid paying for lunch.)
It wouldn't be me.
(How much did he pay this time?)
Out of the eight people... It wouldn't be me.
(Payment booth)
I have to pay no matter what.
I have to pay. I can't pay for everything at the end.
But...
I want to pay a small amount, but I'm scared.
I'll pay the same amount. I'll pay 25 dollars.
(Jong Kook plays safe and pays 25 dollars.)
We have to help Jae Seok...
guess the right person.
- That's right. - Okay.
How much do you think he will pay?
- He said he'll pay a lot. - He'll pay a lot.
- He'll pay a lot. - Jong kook...
It'll still be around 20 to 30 dollars.
He said he'll pay 50 dollars.
(Really?)
We could pay an average of... Thirty dollars?
Thirty dollars.
If we pay 30 dollars each, 3 times 7 is 27.
- It'll be 270 dollars. - Then...
Seok Jin already paid without hearing this.
It's over for him.
(If he's paid below the average, he'd be caught right away.)
If we pay 30 or 40 dollars, Seok Jin will be flustered.
He'll know the amount.
(Laughing)
(He becomes the suspect before the investigation starts.)
- I wrote... - Thirty dollars.
just enough so I wouldn't get caught.
I shouldn't think much about this. I should write a large amount.
I'll write 20 dollars.
Since I paid less...
at the beginning,
I'll still pay less.
It's all or nothing.
I'll just have fun.
(She paid nothing!)
(If she doesn't get caught, she can overtake Jae Seok,)
(who is in 1st place!)
I paid just enough.
- Really? - You took a while.
(She puts on an act and sits down.)
You have to pay quite a lot this time, Ji Eun.
Ji Eun was cool earlier.
I paid enough.
(Following Ji Eun who paid nothing, the others also finish paying!)
(Jae Seok comes in last.)
The amount you'll pay...
out of the total amount...
- of 307 dollars... - Yes?
is 209.2 dollars.
It's 209.2 dollars. That's not bad. It's 209.2 dollars.
(The members paid 97.80 dollars.)
I have no clue. I think I should go there first.
I paid about ten dollars.
- I really paid a lot. - Your eyes...
- are full of lies! - I'm telling the truth.
We paid quite a lot, right?
We paid more than you expected, right?
- More than I thought... - You're satisfied, right?
- We paid a lot, right? - You all...
participated very actively.
- Right? - Right?
(Can he catch the person who paid the least?)
- Did we pay a lot? - I participated in the payment.
- Seriously. - Did we pay a lot?
You paid a lot.
The person who paid...
- the lowest amount... - Let's see.
There were two people.
- Two? - They paid the same amount?
(One of them is Ji Eun.)
- The amount they wrote... - I guess they were the same.
They wrote the same amount.
is zero dollars.
(The lowest payment amount: 0 dollars)
What?
(Someone else besides Ji Eun also paid nothing!)
- Goodness. - They took the risk.
(Watching closely)
- Goodness. - This is fun.
(The five of them react rather strongly.)
- Jae Seok. - I'd be at a disadvantage.
There are two people.
- You have to catch them. - There are two of them.
(Who's the other person that paid nothing?)
They're among us.
- There are two of them. - It's easier.
It wasn't me. It wasn't me, Jae Seok.
I just need to catch one person now.
(Jae Seok remains in 1st place if he catches 1 of the 2!)
I should pick someone with a higher chance.
You have to catch them.
It's good that there are two people.
- I have better odds. - That's right.
- Haha. - Haha and Se Chan.
(Detective Yu starts his deduction.)
- Haha and Se Chan. - If it goes like this,
(Not me.)
it's always Haha or me.
- Seok Sam. - Alibi.
- Alibi. - I...
I don't remember the exact amount, but I wrote about 7 to 8 dollars.
- How could you not remember that? - How could you not remember that?
I don't remember. I don't want to remember it.
It's strange that he doesn't remember.
- I don't want to remember. - It's strange.
(He deleted the payment amount from his head?)
- How can you not remember? - He doesn't want to remember.
- About 7 to 8 dollars. - I think...
From what I see, Seok Jin has very little reason to do that.
Of course. I have no reason.
He's got over 300 dollars saved up.
- I see. - Right.
There's no reason for him to push it...
(Detective Yu's sharp radar gets to work.)
and go that far right now.
Of course. I'm fully buried in debt.
- Ye Eun. - You know,
(Next suspect, Ji Ye Eun)
I didn't even think of spending zero dollars.
Why would I ever spend zero dollars?
Why?
I don't have the guts to pull off something like that.
That's true.
(He agrees.)
- She's right about that. - I spent tens of dollars.
(She can never fool Detective Yu because she has the heart of paper.)
That's plausible.
(He moves on to the next target.)
It's me again?
He's always like this.
- He picks me whenever he does this. - You seem...
- quite flustered now. - All right.
(Calm down.)
- All right. - Okay.
- You're blushing. - You can ask me questions.
(Se Chan gets overly flustered even before he's asked a question.)
- Now... - He's blushing.
- His face... - Here's why. Listen to me.
- First... - Here's why.
(Suspicious)
- You're blushing a lot. - His face is all red.
(Laughing at the unexpected help)
You're always...
He blushed all the way down to his knees.
- That's because of the ice. - Even your knees are red.
I went into the ice bucket.
(Is Se Chan, who is flushing, the culprit?)
- He can't lie. - I mean it.
All right then.
- Hang on. - Interrogate me a little more.
(Let go.)
He got caught.
- I think I caught one for sure. - It's not me.
It wasn't me.
- You're blushing. - No.
His face is all red.
(Approaching)
(Right then, Detective Yu closes in on the real culprit.)
- Ji Eun. - Then, there are...
- two grandmas? - I didn't even know...
- I could pay zero dollars. - What?
I didn't know it was possible.
(Watching closely)
I thought the minimum amount was one cent.
And since I already caught Seok Jin earlier,
I have no reason to take any risks now.
That makes sense.
(But he doesn't let his guard down easily.)
I'm curious.
- Seriously, it's not me. - You can pick me then.
(Fully utilizing her acting skills)
Ji Eun?
- I have no reason to do that. - It's too risky for Ji Eun.
(Detective Yu's gut feelings got him closer to the culprit!)
- It's risky. - Why would I do that?
Right?
I'll show you my bankbook. It's not me.
- I think she's serious. - It's not me, seriously.
(Ji Eun makes a bold move!)
- But this is... - Take a look.
- Look. - I don't think it's her.
(Ddochi is completely fooled.)
- It's not me. - This is difficult.
- I don't think it's Ji Eun. - I didn't do it.
(She boldly escapes his suspicion!)
- Are you sure? - Yes.
(Detective Yu shifts his gaze at this moment.)
- Is it Jong Kook? - Really?
I have no reason to do that.
(Chuckling)
(He caught sight of Ssaebssaeb's face.)
Why is he looking at me?
I'm telling you. I have no reason to do that at this moment.
(I caught you.)
- He's... - I saw him.
- You saw what? - I just saw him.
(Flustered)
He just tried to avoid my eyes.
Se Chan just pulled that exact move...
(Ssaebssaeb has displayed many signs of anxiousness.)
he always does every time I've caught him before.
(Detective Yu becomes very sure.)
- He's always suspicious of me. - He deliberately looked away.
All right.
- It's Yang Se Chan! - Really?
- Is it Se Chan? - I have no reason to take a risk.
(Feeling wronged?)
(Grinning)
Yang Se Chan.
(He picks Se Chan when she almost got caught.)
- I don't think it's Se Chan. - Yang Se Chan.
I don't think it's him.
- I just saw his gaze. - You did?
(Very sure)
(Is Yang Se Chan the member who paid 0 dollars?)
- Yang Se Chan. - I'll announce the results.
- Yang Se Chan. - Is Yang Se Chan...
- the member who paid zero dollars? - Is it him?
Please.
Is it him?
- Wrong. - Please.
- No. - It's him.
(He successfully catches Se Chan, who paid 0 dollars.)
See? I told you.
Unbelievable.
(Was it really Ssaebssaeb?)
See? I told you.
- Unbelievable. - He is...
- How did you know? - I will...
- never do this again with Jae Seok. - How did you know?
I'll make my move now.
I'll pay zero dollars.
(Se Chan paid 0 dollars to make his final move.)
(He even practiced his pocker face not to get caught.)
- See? - He's so sharp.
(But Detective Yu's facial analysis caught him!)
I wasn't sure at first.
- Then you saw through him? - He did it again at the end.
- He's a Se Chan hunter. - When I...
looked at Se Chan,
(Profiler Jae Seok specializes in Se Chan.)
he deliberately looked away.
- He's really sharp. - He can never fool Jae Seok.
(Thanks to him, she's not caught.)
- Jae Seok is like a real cop. - I got it.
- This is crazy. I can't do this. - Se Chan.
- Yang Se Chan. - Why did you do that?
- Why did he do a meaningless thing? - Why?
I wanted to try...
overcoming this.
I wanted to make Jae Seok fail to catch me.
But I failed to overcome it.
(No matter how hard he tries, Jae Seok knows him inside out.)
I just can't do this.
I'll never do it again.
You can never overcome it.
(At the end of a suspenseful deduction,)
Yang Se Chan.
(Jae Seok secures 1st place with a successful arrest.)
I caught him.
He's really good at this.
Now, the Running Balls will be added...
based on the spending ranks.
Number 1 has 5 balls.
- Numbers 2 and 3 get 10 balls each. - We don't know how it turns out.
- Numbers 4, 5, and 6 get 15 balls. - That's a lot.
- It's a lot. - It's a lot.
- Numbers 7, 8, and 9 get 20 balls. - We don't know it yet.
And number 10 gets 25 balls.
Am I the only one with a different count?
We will draw three balls to determine the penalty recipients.
(Drawing the lucky 3 people who'll receive the penalty)
- All right. This is the first. - Jae Seok.
(Drawing the first penalty recipient)
Is this for real or a practice round?
- It's for real. - It's for real.
Let's go.
(The penalty balls have been added based on their final ranks.)
All right. We're doing this for real.
Okay.
(Nervous)
- It can be anyone. - Anyone can be picked.
(Penalty Ball Count: 5, 10, 15, 20, and 25 balls)
- We got one. - It's out.
(Is it Seok Sam with 25 Running Balls?)
It's not me. Please.
- Who is it? - At least tell us the gender.
(Or the lower-ranking 3 members with 20 balls?)
At least the gender.
(Who is the first person to receive the penalty?)
Did you draw all three balls?
Is it a man or a woman?
Jung Eun Ji.
(Oh, no.)
How many balls did you have?
- How many? - She was in third place.
(Eun Ji in 3rd place beats the odds.)
Ten balls.
Jung Eun Ji, with ten balls, is picked.
- I have 25 balls. - We don't know it yet.
(Is this real?)
This is the worst case.
- This is... - Me?
(The bottom ranks with double the balls survived.)
- Seok Jin. - I'll draw the rest.
This is... How did this happen to Eun Ji?
I'm scared.
- I was in third place. - We don't know it yet.
Next.
(Drawing the second penalty recipient)
It's out.
(The bottom 4 smoothly dodged the 1st penalty.)
- All right. - It's out.
(Will they beat the odds again?)
- Who is it? - Why are you looking at me?
- All right. - It's out. Turn it off.
If I get picked, it will be the worst.
- I don't think it's me. - Did you see it?
- I didn't look. - That's the worst.
But it will be fun if you're picked.
- It's fun. - Yu Jae Seok.
(Who is the second penalty recipient to deliver the big laugh?)
- It will be fun if it's you. - Yu Jae Seok.
It will be fun if it's you.
- Yang Se Chan. - Gosh, seriously!
I hate it!
I hate seeing myself get a penalty every week.
We have one person left.
(The bottom dodged it again.)
I hate it!
(With the odds back to normal, his penalty streak continues today.)
We have one person left.
I hate it so much.
All right.
The last one.
(In 10th place)
Seok Jin is not picked?
(A battle among the bottom rank...)
I'm still safe.
- Seok Jin survived? - It has to be him this time.
(with the highest chance to be picked!)
Kim Jong Kook!
(In 7th place)
- Kim Jong Kook! - It's out.
(Please)
It has to be him.
(The fateful draw for the very last spot)
Ji Ye Eun.
- All right. - It'll be fun if it's Haha.
There are so many balls that we don't know who it will be.
- Lee Ju Yeon. - No.
(The top ranker is nervous too.)
- Ji Ye Eun. - It's out. Ji Ye Eun.
(His penalty partner)
(Nobody can let their guard down!)
- Jee Seok Jin. - Haha is also good.
- Haha is also fun. - Jee Seok Jin or Haha.
Please. Anything but a repeat.
(A meaningful expression)
Yu Jae Seok?
- It's Yu Jae Seok. - It's Yu Jae Seok.
(Is it Jae Seok in 1st place against all odds?)
- It's Yu Jae Seok. - Yu Jae Seok.
- But... - Yu Jae Seok?
(Nervous)
- Why? - Is it me?
Ji Ye Eun.
No!
(It's Ddochi, Se Chan's go-to penalty partner.)
Oh, no.
Seok Jin survived.
- How did you survive? - He survived.
(Seok Sam with 25 balls survived.)
Seok Jin survived when he had 25 balls.
(Defying all the odds, Seok Sam snatched good luck.)
- Ji Ye Eun. - Ji Ye Eun.
(I thought I'd avoided it today.)
How did Ye Eun get picked?
(The penalty soulmates bound by relentless fate)
(Today, they collected another attendance stamp for penalties.)
You look cool.
- Ye Eun... - How many balls did you have?
(She resents her fate for the penalty.)
I had 15 balls.
I'm so jealous of Seok Jin.
(Depressed)
What's the penalty?
Today's penalty is...
soaking feet in ice water while writing a 1,000-letter essay...
on your summer getaway.
One, two, three.
All right.
(Putting their feet into the slushy cold water)
(Groaning)
This is so cold!
This is crazy.
I can't think of anything to write.
My brain is freezing.
It was so hot today.
- Where did we go? - Please turn the AC off.
(Brain freeze)
"I did."
(They write things down furiously before frostbite hits.)
What should I say? I just need one more letter.
- "Unchanging..." - "Unchanging dream."
I'll end it like this.
"It was scorching hot today,"
(Cold-feet reading starts.)
"but going into Gwangmyeong Cave..."
- "was so cool and pretty." - This is beautiful.
"It was also my first time visiting Anyang today,"
"and the chicken soup was so delicious."
"Chatting on the bus ride together..."
"brought back memories of riding the bus with school friends."
"I wanted to fool Jae Seok..."
"and took my shot, but it failed."
"I will get my act together."
"An unchanging dream for the future."
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We thank Lee Ju Yeon, Jung Eun Ji, and Kim Ji Eun for cool laughter.)
(This summer)
A man.
A gift for Kang Chan Hee.
Let's do this.
- We have to give him a gift. - Right.
A cameraman.
(Only if we achieve victory...)
It's done. Oh, no.
Hey, will you do it right?
(will his gift be unlocked.)
A gift.
(But a treacherous path awaits!)
- Ulleungdo. - Wrong.
- Dokdo. - Wrong.
Hey!
- It's all your fault! - It's a lot.
You can't be like this.
(With a new troll popping up every single minute,)
If you couldn't do it, you should've practiced.
(Screaming)
Ji Hyo, run.
(it's time to show the true power of this 16-year veteran crew!)
Run! Hurry!
This is the last shot.
Dad!
Dad, are you watching me?
(The oldest member finally resorts to unleash his ultimate move.)
Dad!
Dad, this is an important moment.
(A tear-jerking epic that would make even Homer weep)
- Mom! - Seok Jin.
(A touching story dedicated to one man's gift)
Look at me, you two.
- We have to give Chan Hee a gift. - He's right.
(Will they be able to deliver the news of their victory?)
- Okay. - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Jae Seok!
(Stay Strong, Chan Hee!)
(Running Man)